{
  "trivia": [
    {
      "answer": "runway",
      "category": "Americanisms",
      "question": "Britains say 'tarmac'; Americans say .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "current",
      "category": "Analogies",
      "question": "Analogy: 'Ancient' is to 'old' as 'recent' is to .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "vixen",
      "category": "Analogies",
      "question": "Bull - cow as fox - .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "passersby",
      "category": "Analogies",
      "question": "Goose - geese as passerby - .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "neck",
      "category": "Anatomy",
      "question": "Your  holds your head to your shoulders.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "architecture",
      "category": "Arts",
      "question": "In what field of study would you find \"flying buttresses\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "architecture",
      "category": "Arts",
      "question": "The study of building design is .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Venus de Milo",
      "category": "Arts",
      "question": "This statue was found on the Greek island of Melos in 1820.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Corinthian",
      "category": "Arts",
      "question": "Three main types of Greek columns are Doric, Ionic, and .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Rembrandt",
      "category": "Arts",
      "question": "What Dutch master painted 64 self-portraits?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Paris",
      "category": "Arts",
      "question": "Where is the Louvre located?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Leonardo #da Vinci#",
      "category": "Arts",
      "question": "Who painted the Mona Lisa?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Libra",
      "category": "Astrology",
      "question": "What is the only sign in the zodiac which doesn't represent a living thing?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "April",
      "category": "Astrology",
      "question": "Which month has a diamond as a birthstone?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "comet",
      "category": "Astronomy",
      "question": "A heavenly body moving under the attraction of the Sun and consisting of a nucleus and a tail is a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "yes",
      "category": "Astronomy",
      "question": "Does Uranus have an aurora?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Neptune",
      "category": "Astronomy",
      "question": "From 1979 until 2000 the most distant planet from the earth was .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "nine",
      "category": "Astronomy",
      "question": "How many planets are there in our solar system?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "north",
      "category": "Astronomy",
      "question": "If you're in the northern hemisphere, Polaris, the North Star, can be found by looking which direction?",
      "regexp": "(nine|9)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Jupiter",
      "category": "Astronomy",
      "question": "Name the largest planet in the solar system.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "saturn",
      "category": "Astronomy",
      "question": "Name the second-largest planet in the solar system.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Milky Way",
      "category": "Astronomy",
      "question": "Our galaxy is commonly known as the .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Ursa Major",
      "category": "Astronomy",
      "question": "The Big Dipper is part of what constellation?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Polaris",
      "category": "Astronomy",
      "question": "The North Star is also known as .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Mars",
      "category": "Astronomy",
      "question": "The fourth planet from the sun is .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Orion",
      "category": "Astronomy",
      "question": "The name for the group of stars which form a hunter with a club and shield is .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Mercury",
      "category": "Astronomy",
      "question": "The planet closest to the sun is .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Andromeda",
      "category": "Astronomy",
      "question": "The spiral galaxy nearest ours is the  galaxy.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Moon",
      "category": "Astronomy",
      "question": "The tides on the earth's oceans are actually created by gravitational pull from the .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Pleiades",
      "category": "Astronomy",
      "question": "This cluster of stars is also known as the Seven Sisters.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Comet #Halley#",
      "category": "Astronomy",
      "question": "This comet appears every 76.3 years.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Venus",
      "category": "Astronomy",
      "question": "This planet's diameter is most equal to that of the earth's.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "great bear",
      "category": "Astronomy",
      "question": "What does \"Ursa Major\" mean in everyday English?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "constellation",
      "category": "Astronomy",
      "question": "What is the astronomical name for a group of stars?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "black hole",
      "category": "Astronomy",
      "question": "What is the name for the theoretical end-product of the gravitational collapse of a massive star?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "asteroids",
      "category": "Astronomy",
      "question": "What is the name used to describe the \"minor planets\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "atmosphere",
      "category": "Astronomy",
      "question": "What is the ocean of air around the earth called?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "meteors",
      "category": "Astronomy",
      "question": "What is the proper name for falling stars?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "orbit",
      "category": "Astronomy",
      "question": "What is the term for the path followed a by a small body around a massive body in space?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "tides",
      "category": "Astronomy",
      "question": "What phenomenon is caused by the gravitational attraction of the moon?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Jupiter",
      "category": "Astronomy",
      "question": "What planet boasts the Great Red Spot?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "female",
      "category": "Bet you don't know ;-)",
      "question": "The two sexes of humans are male and ?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "nicotine",
      "category": "Biochemistry",
      "question": "This poisonous, oily liquid occurs in tobacco leaves.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Haemoglobin",
      "category": "Biochemistry",
      "question": "This protein makes the blood red in color.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "navel",
      "category": "Biology",
      "question": "Every human has one of these on their tummies.",
      "regexp": "Ha?emoglobin"
    },
    {
      "answer": "seven",
      "category": "Biology",
      "question": "How many large holes are in your head?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "protoplasm",
      "category": "Biology",
      "question": "This complex substance makes up all living things.",
      "regexp": "(seven|7)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "98.6",
      "category": "Biology",
      "question": "What is normal body temperature for an adult human (in degrees fahrenheit)?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "grafting",
      "category": "Botany",
      "question": "The practice of joining the parts of two plants to make them grow as one is called .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "lichen",
      "category": "Botany",
      "question": "These flowerless plants grow on bare rocks and tree stumps.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "strawberry",
      "category": "Botany",
      "question": "This fruit has its seeds on the outside.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "conifers",
      "category": "Botany",
      "question": "This term means 'cone-bearing trees'.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "grapefruit",
      "category": "Botany",
      "question": "What fruit bear the latin name \"citrus grandis\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "three hundred and sixty six",
      "category": "Calendar",
      "question": "How many days where there in 1976?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Theodore",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Alvin & Simon had a brother called .",
      "regexp": "(three hundred (and )?sixty[- ]six|366)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Woody Woodpecker",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "An Andy Panda cartoon gave birth to a famous, cantankerous bird. Name him.",
      "regexp": "(theodore|theo)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Chumley",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "An adventurous penguin named Tennessee Tuxedo had a sidekick named ?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Mars",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "An alien creature in a funny hat has opposed both Bugs Bunny and Daffy Duck.  Where is he from?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Ham Gravy",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Before Olive Oil met Popeye she was engaged to someone.  Who was he?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "John",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Benny and Cecil were at odds with whom?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Yosemite Sam",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Bugs always finds himself at the wrong end of a gun, usually toted by either Elmer Fudd or who?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Wendy",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Casper the Friendly Ghost frolicked with which witch?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Pepe le Pew",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Charles Boyer inspired a cartoon skunk. Who?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Shadow",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Famous Phrases: Who knows? The .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Godzilla",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Gadzookie has a large, green friend. Who is he?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Tom and Jerry",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Hanna-Barbera rose to fame by creating what duo for MGM?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "#mental# powers",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "How does Wonder Woman control her invisible airplane?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Ding",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "In the cartoons who was Hokie Wolf's sidekick?",
      "regexp": "(mental|mind|brain|tele(pathy|kinesis))"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Philadelphia",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "In what city does Fat Albert live?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Ero",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Mentor of Titan had two children in the Marvel comics, Thanos and ?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "General Halftrack",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Miss Buckley is secretary to what commanding officer?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Oola",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Name Alley Oop's girl friend.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Irving",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Name Cathy's on again/off again boy friend?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Mr and Mrs #Wilson#",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Name Dennis the Menace's next door neighbors.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Daisy",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Name Donald Duck's girlfriend?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Snert",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Name Hagar the Horrible's dog.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Kickapoo Joy Juice",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Name Li'l Abner's favorite Indian drink.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "The #Snork#s",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Name the European hit, now an animated series about underwater people.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "The #Skypad# Apartments",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Name the apartments the Jetson's live in.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Chopper",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Name the dog in the Yankee Doodle cartoons.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Speedy Gonzalez",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Name the fastest mouse in all of Mexico.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Rick",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Name the ranger who was always after Yogi Bear.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Bedrock",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Name the town that Fred, Wilma, Barney, and Betty lived in.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Captain Kangaroo",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "On what T.V. show could Tom Terrific be found?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Brutus",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Popeye's chief adversary has two names, Bluto and ?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Petunia",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Porky Pig had a girlfriend named .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Dick Tracy",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Tess Trueheart married which plainclothes detective?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "steam",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "What came out of Milton's head?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Screwball Squirrel",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "What character did Tex Avery first create upon arriving at MGM?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Lois (of Hi and #Lois#)",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "What comic strip character is Beetle Bailey's sister?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "A family #inheritance#",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "What did Dagwood give up to marry Blondie?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Chuck",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "What did Peppermint Patty always call Charlie Brown?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Pennyworth",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "What is Batman's butler Alfred's last name.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Oop",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "What is Blondie's maiden name?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Mitchell",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "What is Dennis the Menace's last name?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "fireman",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "What is Smokey Stover's job?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Fred",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "What is Super Chicken's partners name?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Thelma",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "What is the mother's name in Family Circus?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Horse",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "What is the name of Duddley Do-Right's horse?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Barf",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "What is the name of the Family Circus's dog?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "great dane",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "What kind of dog is Scooby Doo?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "venus flytrap",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "What type of plant does Broom Hilda sell?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "#You're dispicable#!",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "What was Daffy Duck's favorite insult?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "A #tree#",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "What was George of the Jungle always running in to?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Steamboat Willie",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "What was the first cartoon to feature sound?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Shep",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "What was the name of George of the Jungle's pet elephant?",
      "regexp": "Steamboat Will(ie|y)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "The #Mach Five#",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "What was the name of Speed Racer's car?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Li'l Folks",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "What was the original name Charles Schultz had for Peanuts?",
      "regexp": "(Mach (Five|5))"
    },
    {
      "answer": "cousin",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "What was the relationship between Superman and Supergirl?",
      "regexp": "Li'?l Folks"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Sylvester",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "When Tweety exclaimed, \"I thought I saw a putty tat!\", who did he see?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "El KaBong",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "When danger appeared, Quick Draw McGraw became which super hero?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "#police# officer",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "When not a Birdman, what does Ray Randall do for a living?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "#shoeshine# boy",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "When not fighting crime, what did Underdog do for a living?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Frostbite Falls",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Where are Rocket J. Squirel and Bullwinkle Moose from?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "#Metropolis# University",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Where did Clark Kent attend college?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Imgwee Gwee Valley",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Where did George of the Jungle live?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "supermarket",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Where did Mighty Mouse get his superpowers?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "What'samatta University",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Where do Rocky and Bullwinkle play football?",
      "regexp": "super ?market"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Spacely Sprockets",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Where does George Jetson work?",
      "regexp": "What'?samatta U"
    },
    {
      "answer": "#Jellystone# Park",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Where does Yogi Bear Live?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Beetle Bailey",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Which comic strip was banned from \"Stars and Stripes\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Peacemaker",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Which superhero loves peace enough to kill for it?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Captain Marvel",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Who always tried to kill Krazy Kat?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Scrooge",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Who is Donald Duck's uncle?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Linus",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Who is Sally Brown's sweet baboo?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "#Scrappy# Doo",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Who is Scooby Doo's nephew??",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "The #Red Baron#",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Who is Snoopy's arch enemy?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Beetle Bailey",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Who is stationed at Camp Swampy in the comic strips?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Jack and Jill",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Who runs Andy Capp's favorite pub?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Porky Pig",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Who says, \"Th-th-th-that's all folks!\"",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Chill",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Who shot Bruce Wayne's parents?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Muttley",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Who was Dick Dastardly's pet?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Percy",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Who was always trying to get rent from Andy Capp?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Rick Jones",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Who was the Hulk's first friend?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Walt Disney",
      "category": "Cartoon Trivia",
      "question": "Who was the original voice of Mickey Mouse?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "water",
      "category": "Chemistry",
      "question": "Hydrogen Hydroxide is more commonly known as what?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "air",
      "category": "Chemistry",
      "question": "Nitrogen, a poisonous gas, makes up 78% of the  that we breathe.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "lye",
      "category": "Chemistry",
      "question": "Sodium Hydroxide is more commonly known as .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "baking soda",
      "category": "Chemistry",
      "question": "Sodium bicarbonate is better known as .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "desalination",
      "category": "Chemistry",
      "question": "The process of removing salt from sea water is known as .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "molecule",
      "category": "Chemistry",
      "question": "The smallest portion of a substance capable of existing independently and retaining its original properties is a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "alchemy",
      "category": "Chemistry",
      "question": "This ancient attempt to transmute base metals into gold was called .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "uranium",
      "category": "Chemistry",
      "question": "This is the heaviest naturally occurring element.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Sn",
      "category": "Chemistry",
      "question": "This is the symbol for tin.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "carbon monoxide",
      "category": "Chemistry",
      "question": "This poisonous gas is in the exhaust fumes from cars.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "soda water",
      "category": "Chemistry",
      "question": "Water containing carbon dioxide under pressure is called  .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "acid",
      "category": "Chemistry",
      "question": "What is it that turns blue litmus paper red?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "TNT",
      "category": "Chemistry",
      "question": "What is the abbreviation for trinitrotoluene?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Cu",
      "category": "Chemistry",
      "question": "What is the chemical symbol for copper?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Au",
      "category": "Chemistry",
      "question": "What is the chemical symbol for gold?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "nitrogen",
      "category": "Chemistry",
      "question": "What is the main component of air?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "mercury",
      "category": "Chemistry",
      "question": "What is the more scientific name for quicksilver?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Fe",
      "category": "Chemistry",
      "question": "What is the symbol for iron in chemistry?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Ag",
      "category": "Chemistry",
      "question": "What is the symbol for silver?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Rudolph",
      "category": "Christmas",
      "question": "Name the loner rebel reindeer with the red shiny nose.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "north",
      "category": "Christmas",
      "question": "Santa Claus reportedly lives at the  Pole.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Beetle Bailey",
      "category": "Comic Strip Trivia",
      "question": "What comic strip is set at Camp Swampy?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "monitor",
      "category": "Computer Science",
      "question": "That big square thing you're staring at right now is called a ?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "IRC",
      "category": "Computer Science",
      "question": "The Internet Relay Chat Program, which normally connects to port 6667, is more commonly known as .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "nationalism",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "--isms:  Exalting one's country above all others.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "atheism",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "--isms:  The belief that there is no God.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "agnosticism",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "--isms:  The theory that man cannot prove the existence of a god.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "theism",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "-ism: The belief in the existence of a god or gods.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "alcoholism",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "-isms: A diseased condition resulting from the use of beverages such as whiskey.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "fascism",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "-isms: A one-party system of government in which control is maintained by force and regimentation.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "rheumatism",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "-isms: A painful stiffness of the muscles and joints",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "criticism",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "-isms: A severe or unfavorable judgment.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "capitalism",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "-isms: An economic system characterized by private ownership and competition.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "commercialism",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "-isms: Excessive emphasis on financial gain.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "fanaticism",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "-isms: Excessive enthusiasm or zeal for a cause.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "botulism",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "-isms: Poisoning caused by a toxin in improperly prepared food.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "socialism",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "-isms: Public ownership of the basic means of production, distribution, and exchange.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "asceticism",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "-isms: The belief in living a very austere and self-denying life.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "barrette",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "A clip, shaped like a bar to keep a woman's hair in place is a .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "hair",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "A depilatory is a substance used for removing .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "transformer",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "A device used to change the voltage of alternating currents is a .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "beret",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "A flat, round hat sometimes worn by soldiers is a .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "oligarchy",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "A government in which power is restricted to a few is a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "octogenarian",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "A person in his eighties is called a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "arsonist",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "A person who starts fires maliciously is a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "kleptomaniac",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "A person with a strong desire to steal is a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "boxer",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "A pugilist is a .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "font",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "A receptacle for holy water is a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "raisin",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "A sun-dried grape is known as a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "acronym",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "A word like 'NASA' formed from the initials of other words is a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "heights",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "Acrophobia is a fear of .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "knowledge",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "An \"omniscient\" person has unlimited .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "wind velocity",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "An anemometer measures  .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "taxidermist",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "An animal stuffer is a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "easel",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "An artist supports his canvas on a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "odometer",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "An instrument on a car to measure the distance travelled is called a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "males",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "Androphobia is the fear of .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "extinct",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "Animals that once existed but don't exist now are said to be .",
      "regexp": "(men|males?)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "amulet",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "Any object worn as a charm may be called a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "books",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "Bibliophobia is a fear of .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "thunder",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "Brontophobia is the fear of .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "ring dating",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "Dendrochronology is better known as .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "fur",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "Doraphobia is the fear of .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "freedom",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "Eleutherophobia is a fear of .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "naked bodies",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "Gymnophobia is the fear of .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "dunes",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "Hills and ridges composed of drifting sand are known as .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "fish",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "Ichthyology is the study of .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "felony",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "Legal Terms: A crime more serious than a misdemeanor.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "contract",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "Legal Terms: A formal agreement enforceable by law.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "codicil",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "Legal Terms: A supplement to a will.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "jury",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "Legal Terms: The people chosen to render a verdict in a court.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "embezzle",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "Legal Terms: To steal property entrusted to one's care.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "dentist",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "Name the pain-inflicting person you go to to get your teeth fixed.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "toilet",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "Name the porceilan chair you sit on at least once a day.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "astrologer",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "One who tells fortunes by the stars is a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "rodents",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "Rats, mice, beavers, and squirrels are all .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "lithography",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "The art of tracing designs and taking impressions of them is .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "aglet",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "The covering on the tip of a shoelace is a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "circumference",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "The distance around the outside of a circle is its .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "aerospace",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "The earth's atmosphere and the space beyond is known as .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "echo",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "The effect produced when sound is reflected back is known as a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "deja vu",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "The feeling of having experienced something before is known as .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "pharmacy",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "The science of preparing and dispensing drugs is .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "logistics",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "The science of providing men, equipment and supplies for military operations is called .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "psychology",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "The study of human behaviour is .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "archaeology",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "The study of human pre-history is .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "entomology",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "The study of insects is .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "optics",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "The study of light and its relation to sight is called .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "anthropology",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "The study of man and culture is known as .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "physics",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "The study of natural phenomena: motion, forces, light, sound, etc. is called .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "botany",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "The study of plants is .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "theology",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "The study of religion is .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "acoustics",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "The study of sound is .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "chemistry",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "The study of the composition of substances and the changes that they undergo is .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "geography",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "The study of the earth's physical divisions into mountains, seas, etc. is .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "physiology",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "The study of the manner in which organisms carry on their life processes is .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "legend",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "The symbols used on a map are explained by the .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "chemotherapy",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "The treatment of disease by chemical substances which are toxic to the causative micro-organisms is called .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "bob",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "The weight at the end of a pendulum is a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "levee",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "The wide wall built along the banks of rivers to stop flooding is a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "cloud",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "The word \"cumulus\" refers to a type of .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "calliper",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "This instrument is used for measuring the distance between two points, on a curved surface.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "barometer",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "This instrument measures atmospheric pressure.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "anemometer",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "This instrument measures the velocity of the wind.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "claustrophobia",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "This is the fear of enclosed spaces.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "mayday",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "This word is used as the international radio distress call.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "schizophrenia",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "This word means \"split personality\".",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "shoe",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "Throat, foxing, and platform are parts of a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "poison",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "Toxiphobia is a fear of .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "cigar bands",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "What does a brandophile collect?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "the #sun#",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "What does a heliologist study?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "birds",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "What does an ornithologist study?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "tourniquet",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "What is a device to stem the flow of blood called?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "prune",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "What is a dried plum called?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "pen",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "What is a female swan called?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "octagon",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "What is a figure with eight equal sides called?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "epitaph",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "What is another name for a tombstone inscription?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "time",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "What is measured by a chronometer?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "bonsai",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "What is the common name for a Japanese dwarf tree?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "northern lights",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "What is the common name for the Aurora Borealis?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "sleepwalker",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "What is the common term for a \"somnambulist\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "tributary",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "What is the name for a branch of a river?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "genetics",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "What is the study of heredity called?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "paleontology",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "What is the study of prehistoric plants and animals called?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "capon",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "What is the term for a castrated rooster?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "meteorology",
      "category": "Definitions",
      "question": "Which science studies weather?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "iron",
      "category": "Domestic Metallurgy",
      "question": "Name the clothing wrinkle remover that sounds like a kind of metal.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "3",
      "category": "Don't Strain Yourself Thinking ;-)",
      "question": "A 3 1/2\" floppy disk measures  and 1/2 inches across.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "brown",
      "category": "Don't Strain Yourself Thinking ;-)",
      "question": "A brown crayon is what color?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "smoke",
      "category": "Don't Strain Yourself Thinking ;-)",
      "question": "A smoke detector will alarm if it detects .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "water",
      "category": "Don't Strain Yourself Thinking ;-)",
      "question": "A water heater keeps  warm for you.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "french",
      "category": "Don't Strain Yourself Thinking ;-)",
      "question": "Although not all come from France,  fries are often served with hamburgers.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "alarm",
      "category": "Don't Strain Yourself Thinking ;-)",
      "question": "An  clock usually wakes you in the morning.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "boston",
      "category": "Don't Strain Yourself Thinking ;-)",
      "question": "During the American Revolution, the Boston Tea Party took place in  Harbor.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "abbreviation",
      "category": "Don't Strain Yourself Thinking ;-)",
      "question": "How do you spell abbreviation?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "twelve",
      "category": "Don't Strain Yourself Thinking ;-)",
      "question": "How many pencils are there in a dozen?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Thornton #Wilder#",
      "category": "Drama",
      "question": "\"Our Town\" is a play by whom?",
      "regexp": "(twelve|12)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Grover's Corners",
      "category": "Drama",
      "question": "The play \"Our Town\" is set where?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "necromancer",
      "category": "Fantasy",
      "question": "What is a sorcerer who deals in black magic called?",
      "regexp": "Grover'?s Corner"
    },
    {
      "answer": "pig",
      "category": "Food",
      "question": "Boston butt, jowl, and picnic ham are parts of a .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "grapefruit",
      "category": "Food and Drink",
      "question": "Even though it tastes nothing like grapes, a  is often eaten for breakfast.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "deer",
      "category": "Food and Drink",
      "question": "From what animal do we get venison?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "sturgeon",
      "category": "Food and Drink",
      "question": "From which fish is caviar obtained?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "cherry",
      "category": "Food and Drink",
      "question": "From which fruit is the liqueur Kirsh made?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "lettuce",
      "category": "Food and Drink",
      "question": "Iceberg, Boston, and Bibb are types of .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "apricot",
      "category": "Food and Drink",
      "question": "Laetrile is associated with the pit of which fruit?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "m",
      "category": "Food and Drink",
      "question": "Little round chocolate candies are known as _&m's.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "condiments",
      "category": "Food and Drink",
      "question": "Mustard, ketchup and onions on a hotdog are all .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "orange",
      "category": "Food and Drink",
      "question": "Name the only fruit named for its color.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "orchid",
      "category": "Food and Drink",
      "question": "Natural vanilla flavoring comes from this plant.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "milk",
      "category": "Food and Drink",
      "question": "Often drunk, this liquid is normally harvested from female cows.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "pig",
      "category": "Food and Drink",
      "question": "Often eaten for breakfast, bacon is actually the flesh of what barnyard animal?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "chicken",
      "category": "Food and Drink",
      "question": "Often eaten for breakfast, the egg comes from what barnyard animal?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "sugar cane",
      "category": "Food and Drink",
      "question": "Rum is made from this plant.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "little worms",
      "category": "Food and Drink",
      "question": "Vermicelli literally means .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "sangria",
      "category": "Food and Drink",
      "question": "What do you get when you add fresh fruit to red wine?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "rice",
      "category": "Food and Drink",
      "question": "What is Japanese \"sake\" made from?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "molasses",
      "category": "Food and Drink",
      "question": "What is the name of the syrup drained from raw sugar?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "almonds",
      "category": "Food and Drink",
      "question": "What kind of nuts are used in marzipan?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "cognac",
      "category": "Food and Drink",
      "question": "Where is the best brandy bottled?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "St. Louis",
      "category": "Food and Drink",
      "question": "Where was Budweiser first brewed?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "mint julep",
      "category": "Fun",
      "question": "Cocktails: Bourbon, sugar and mint make a(n) .",
      "regexp": "St.? Louis"
    },
    {
      "answer": "stinger",
      "category": "Fun",
      "question": "Cocktails: Cognac (brandy) and white creme de menthe make a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "brandy alexander",
      "category": "Fun",
      "question": "Cocktails: Creme de Cacao, cream, and brandy make a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Tom Collins",
      "category": "Fun",
      "question": "Cocktails: Gin and Collins mix make a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "cuba libre",
      "category": "Fun",
      "question": "Cocktails: Rum, lime, and cola drink make a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "margarita",
      "category": "Fun",
      "question": "Cocktails: Triple sec, tequila, and lemon or lime juice make a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "black russian",
      "category": "Fun",
      "question": "Cocktails: Vodka and Kahlua make a .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Harvey Wallbanger",
      "category": "Fun",
      "question": "Cocktails: Vodka, orange juice and Galliano make a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Irish coffee",
      "category": "Fun",
      "question": "Cocktails: Whiskey, hot coffee, and whipped cream make a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "void",
      "category": "Games",
      "question": "A bridge hand with no cards in one suit is said to have a .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "full house",
      "category": "Games",
      "question": "A poker hand consisting of three of a kind and a pair is called a .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "twenty two",
      "category": "Games",
      "question": "How many balls are used in a game of snooker including the cue ball?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "forty two",
      "category": "Games",
      "question": "How many dots are there on a pair of dice?",
      "regexp": "(twenty[- ]two|22)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "sixty four",
      "category": "Games",
      "question": "How many squares are there on a chessboard?",
      "regexp": "(forty[- ]two|42)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "cribbage",
      "category": "Games",
      "question": "If you \"peg out\" what game are you playing?",
      "regexp": "(sixty[- ]four|64)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "flush",
      "category": "Games",
      "question": "In poker five cards of the same suit is called a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "black",
      "category": "Games",
      "question": "In pool, what color is the eight ball?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "poker",
      "category": "Games",
      "question": "In which game might a person have a \"full house\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "chess",
      "category": "Games",
      "question": "In which game or sport are \"Staunton\" pieces used?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "cribbage",
      "category": "Games",
      "question": "In which game or sport can a person be \"skunked\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "tenpin #bowling#",
      "category": "Games",
      "question": "In which sport are terms \"spare\" and \"gutter\" used?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "chess",
      "category": "Games",
      "question": "In which sport or game are the terms: 'pin', 'fork', and 'skewer' used?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "chess",
      "category": "Games",
      "question": "In which sport or game is the term \"rook\" used?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "rope",
      "category": "Games",
      "question": "Name the only flexible murder weapon in the game of \"Cluedo\".",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Miss #Scarlett#",
      "category": "Games",
      "question": "Name the only woman suspect in the game of \"Cluedo\" who isn't married.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Z",
      "category": "Games",
      "question": "These are the two highest valued letters in \"Scrabble\".  \"Q\" and .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "mah jongg",
      "category": "Games",
      "question": "This ancient Chinese game is played with 156 small rectangular tiles.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "clubs",
      "category": "Games",
      "question": "This is the lowest ranking suit in Bridge.",
      "regexp": "mah? ?jong"
    },
    {
      "answer": "castling",
      "category": "Games",
      "question": "This term denotes a chess move in which both the king and the rook are moved.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "turkey",
      "category": "Games",
      "question": "What bowling term means three straight strikes?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "chess",
      "category": "Games",
      "question": "What game or sport is Bobby Fischer identified with?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "two",
      "category": "Games",
      "question": "What number is on the opposite side of the \"five\" on dice?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "nineteen",
      "category": "Games",
      "question": "What score is not possible for a cribbage hand?",
      "regexp": "(two|2)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "rook",
      "category": "Games",
      "question": "Which chess piece is usually valued as 5 points?",
      "regexp": "(nineteen|19)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "twenty questions",
      "category": "Games",
      "question": "Which game usually begins with, \"Is it animal, vegetable, or mineral?\"",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "bark",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Although it doesn't sound like a dog, dust is ornamental wood chips often placed in flowerbeds.",
      "regexp": "(twenty|20) questions"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Chicago",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Chicago Transit Authority is now known as which group?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "driveway",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "If you drive on a parkway, you park on a ?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "petrol",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "To refuel your car you go to a  station.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "#ring# finger",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Wedding rings are normally worn on what finger of your hand?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "books",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "What are catalogued under the Dewey decimal system?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Harvard, Princeton, Yale",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "What are the 3 big colleges of the Ivy League? (name them alphabetically)",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Proctor & Gamble",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "What company makes Pampers disposable diapers?",
      "regexp": "Harvard,? Princeton,?( and)? Yale"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Unidentified Flying Object",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "What do the initials U.F.O stand for?",
      "regexp": "Proctor (&|and) Gamble"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Surface-to-Air Missile",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "What do the letters in SAM missiles refer to?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Internal Revenue Service",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "What does IRS stand for?",
      "regexp": "Surface[- ]to[- ]Air"
    },
    {
      "answer": "north",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "What does a compass needle point to?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Ante Meridian",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "What does the abbreviation a.m. stand for?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Central Intelligence Agency",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "What does the acronym CIA stand for?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "one hundred and forty",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "What is the minimum IQ score for the genius category?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "ampersand",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "What is this sign called \"&\"?",
      "regexp": "(one hundred (and |& )?forty|140)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "dial",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "When using a telephone, you must wait for a  tone before starting your call.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Abraham #Lincoln#",
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Which U.S. president is on the five-dollar bill?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Nova Scotia",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Acadia was the original name of which Canadian province?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Connecticut",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Bridgeport is the largest city in which state?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Barbados",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Bridgetown is the capital of .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Belgium",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Brussels is the capital of which country?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Kentucky",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Frankfort is the capital of which state?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Ecuador",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Guayaquil is the largest city in what country?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Nova Scotia",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Halifax is the capital of which Canadian province?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Cuba",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Havana is the capital of which country?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Gerardus #Mercator#",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "He invented the most common projection for world maps.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Vancouver",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "He visited Australia and New Zealand, then surveyed the Pacific Coast of North America.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "four",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "How many stars are on the flag of New Zealand?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "#4#:00pm",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "If its 4:00pm in Seattle, Washington what time is it in Portland, Oregon?",
      "regexp": "(four|4)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Copenhagen",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In what city are the famous Tivoli Gardens?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Pisa",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In what city is the Leaning Tower?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Washington",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In what city is the Smithsonian Institute?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Canada",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In what country is Banff National Park?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Pakistan",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In what country is Lahore?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "#Myanmar# (formerly known as Burma)",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In what country is Mandalay?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Taiwan",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In what country is Taipei?",
      "regexp": "(Myanmar|Burma)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Canada",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In what country is Thunder Bay?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Denmark",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In what country is the Jutland peninsula?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Vietnam",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In what country is the Mekong River Delta?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Belgium",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In what country is the Waterloo battlefield?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Argentina",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In what country is the highest point in South America?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Argentina",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In what country is the lowest point in South America?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Ethiopia",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In what country is the source of the Blue Nile?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "#Philippine#s",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In what island group is Corregidor?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Rocky",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In what mountain range is Kicking Horse Pass?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "New Hampshire",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In what state is Concord?",
      "regexp": "Rock(y|ies)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Moscow",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In which city is Red Square?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "London",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In which city is Saint Paul's Cathedral?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "London",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In which city is Wembley Stadium?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Venice",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In which city is the Bridge of Sighs?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Toronto",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In which city is the C.N. Tower?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Venice",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In which city is the Canale Grande?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Rome",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In which city is the Colliseum located?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Jerusalem",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In which city is the Wailing Wall?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Venezuela",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In which country is Angel Falls?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "France",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In which country is Brest? (NOT Breast!)",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "India",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In which country is Chennai (formerly Madras)?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Peru",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In which country is Cusco?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Scotland",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In which country is Loch Ness?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "France",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In which country is Normandy?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Japan",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In which country is Sapporo?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Italy",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In which country is the Calabria region?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Tibet",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In which country is the Dalai Lama's palace?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Australia",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In which country is the Great Victoria Desert?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Peru",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In which country is the Machu Picchu?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Mexico",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In which country would you find the Yucatan Peninsula?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "#Indian# Ocean",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In which ocean or sea are the Seychelles?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Pennsylvania",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In which state are Gettysburg and the Liberty Bell?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "New York",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In which state are the Finger Lakes?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Virginia",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In which state is Appomattax?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "North Carolina",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In which state is Cape Hatteras?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Arizona",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In which state is Hoover Dam?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Alaska",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In which state is Mount McKinley?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Washington",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In which state is Mount St. Helens?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Virginia",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In which state is Mount Vernon?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Georgia",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In which state is Stone Mountain?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Washington",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In which state is Walla Walla?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Florida",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In which state is the Kennedy Space Center?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Minnesota",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In which state is the Mayo Clinic?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Arizona",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "In which state is the Painted Desert?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Bay Of #Bengal#",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Into what bay does the Ganges River flow?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Black Sea",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Into what body of water does the Danube River flow?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "#Bering# Sea",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Into what body of water does the Yukon River flow?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "#North# Sea",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Into what sea does the Elbe River flow?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "#Beaufort# Sea",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Into what sea does the Mackenzie River flow?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Sudan",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Khartoum is the capital of which country?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Jamaica",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Kingston is the capital of which country?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Danube",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Linz, Austria is a leading port on which river?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Tagus",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Madrid and Lisbon are both located near this river.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "#pole#s",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Meridians converge at the .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Fiji",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Mount Victoria is the highest peak of this island country.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Turkey",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Name a country which has the same name as a bird.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Alaska",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Name the U.S. state with the smallest population.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Boston",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Name the capital city of Massachusetts.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Providence",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Name the capital city of Rhode Island.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Buenos Aires",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Name the capital of Argentina.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Brasilia",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Name the capital of Brazil.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Rome",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Name the capital of Italy.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Duluth",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Name the city at the west end of Lake Superior.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Australia",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Name the continent that consists of a single country.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Mojave",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Name the desert located in south-east California.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "The #Appalachian#s",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Name the large mountain chain in the eastern U.S.A.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "St. Peter's",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Name the largest cathedral in the world.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Toronto",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Name the largest city in Canada.",
      "regexp": "St.? ?Peter'?s"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Greenland",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Name the largest island in the world.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Eyre",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Name the largest lake in Australia.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Rio Grande",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Name the largest river forming part of the U.S. - Mexican border.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Newfoundland",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Name the last province to become part of Canada.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Yangtze",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Name the longest river in Asia.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Niger",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Name the longest river in Nigeria.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Maine",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Name the most north-easterly of the 48 contiguous states.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "El Salvador",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Name the only Central American country without an Atlantic coastline.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Aegean",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Name the sea between Asia Minor and Greece.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "#Yellow# Sea",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Name the sea between Korea and China.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Beaufort",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Name the sea north of Alaska.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Barents",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Name the sea north of Murmansk, Russia.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Bering",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Name the sea west of Alaska.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Algeria",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Name the second largest country in Africa.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Argentina",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Name the second largest country in South America.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Huron",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Name the second largest lake in North America.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Ontario",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Name the smallest of the Great Lakes.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Gibraltar",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Name the strait joining the Atlantic Ocean and the Mediterranean Sea.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Fuji",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Name the world's most photographed and most climbed mountain.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Bahamas",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Nassau is the capital of which country?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Oahu",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "On what island is Honolulu?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Oahu",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "On what island is Pearl Harbour?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Capri",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "On what island is the Blue Grotto?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Cuba",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "On what island is the U.S. naval base, Guantanamo?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Rushmore",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "On what mountain are four presidents' faces carved?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "The #Iberia#n peninsula",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "On what peninsula are Spain and Portugal located?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Ottawa",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "On what river is the capital city of Canada?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Thames",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "On which river is London, England?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Tiber",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "On which river is Rome located?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Nile",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "On which river is the Aswan High Dam?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Water",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Over 75% of the Earth's surface is covered by some form of .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Morocco",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Rabat is the capital of which country?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "San Francisco",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "San Francisco Bay is located near what city?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "South Korea",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Seoul is the capital of which country?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Grenada",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "St. George's is the capital city of what island country?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Hawaii",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Surfing is believed to have originated here.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "New Zealand",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "The Auckland Islands belong to which country?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Scotland",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "The Hebrides are part of this country.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Greece",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "The Ionian and Cyclades are island groups of which country?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Copenhagen",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "The Little Mermaid is found in the harbour of which city?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Taiwan",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "The Nationalist Chinese occupy this island.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "#Panama# Canal",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "The Thatcher Ferry Bridge crosses what canal?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "50",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "The United States is made up of  states.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Ghana",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "The Volta is the largest river in which country?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Benelux",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "The countries of Belgium, Netherlands, and Luxembourg are together called .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Rhine",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "The longest river in Western Europe is ?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "west",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "The sun sets in the ?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Baffin",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "This Canadian island is the world's fifth largest.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Easter Island",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "This Pacific island's puzzling monoliths attract ethnologists.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Korea",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "This country is divided at the 38th parallel.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Somalia",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "This country occupies the \"horn of Africa\".",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Rwanda",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "This country's flag has a large \"R\" on it.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "international date line",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "This imaginary line approximately follows the 180 degree meridian through the Pacific Ocean.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Niagara Falls",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "This is called the \"Honeymoon Capital\" of the world.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Verrazano Narrows",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "This is the bridge with the longest span in the U.S.A.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "The #Bronx#",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "This is the only borough of New York City that is not on an island.",
      "regexp": "verrazano"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Yokohama",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "This is the port city serving Tokyo.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Buckingham Palace",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "This is the residence of English monarchs.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "#Falkland# Islands",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "This island group is off the east coast of southern South America.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Suez Canal",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "This re-opened in 1975 after being closed for 8 years.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Harlem",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "This section of Manhattan is noted for its Negro and Latin American residents.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Denmark",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "To what country do the Faeroe Islands belong?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Egypt",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "To what country does the Gaza Strip belong?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "false",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "True Or False:  The Easter Bunny is from Easter Island.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "false",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "True Or False:  There are only virgins on the Virgin Islands.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Hudson",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Under what river does the Holland Tunnel run?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Poland",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Warsaw is the capital of what country?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Miami",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What American city is known as Little Havana?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Tokyo",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What Asian city was once called Edo?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Hamilton",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What Canadian city is at the west end of Lake Ontario?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "France",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What European country administers the island of Martinique?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Liechtenstein",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What European country has \"Vaduz\" as its capital city?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Greenwich",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What London borough does the Prime Meridian pass through?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Hartford",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What U.S. city is known as Insurance City?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "San Francisco",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What U.S. city is named after Saint Francis of Assisi?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Minnesota",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What U.S. state is known as The Land of 10,000 Lakes?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Hawaii",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What US state is completely surrounded by the Pacific Ocean?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "#glacier#s",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What are drumlins and eskers formed by?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Arctic, Atlantic, Indian and Pacific",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What are the worlds four oceans - alphabetically?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Persian Gulf",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What body of water borders Saudi Arabia to the east?",
      "regexp": "Arctic,? Atlantic,? Indian(,| and)? Pacific"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Welland",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What canal connects Lake Ontario and Lake Erie?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "#Rio# de Janeiro",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What city boasts the Copacabana Beach and Ipanema?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "San Francisco",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What city is associated with Alcatraz?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Cleveland",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What city is on Lake Erie at the mouth of the Cuyahoga River?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Boston",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What city is the Christian Science Monitor based in?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Moscow",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What city is the Kremlin located in?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Atlanta",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What city was the setting for \"Gone With the Wind\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "red",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What color does the bride wear in China?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Asia",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What continent is Cyprus considered to be part of?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Africa",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What continent is the home to the greatest number of countries?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Taiwan",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What country are the Islands of Quemoy and Matsu part of?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Libya",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What country borders Egypt on the west?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Sudan",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What country borders Egypt to the south?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Greece",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What country does the island of Mykonos belong to?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Tanzania",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What country formed the union of Tanganyika and Zanzibar?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Chile",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What country has the world's most southerly city?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Cambodia",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What country is Phnom Penh the capital of?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Dominican Republic",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What country is Santo Domingo the capital of?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Lebanon",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What country is directly north of Israel?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Canada",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What country is directly north of the continental United States?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Portugal",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What country is directly west of Spain?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Greece",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What country is known as the Hellenic Republic?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Costa Rica",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What country is located between Panama and Nicaragua?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Greece",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What country owns the island of Corfu?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "France",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What country was once known as Gaul?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Morocco",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What country was the setting for \"Casablanca\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Russia",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What country was the setting for \"Doctor Zhivago\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Old Faithful",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What famous geyser erupts regularly at the Yellowstone National Park?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Juneau",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What is the capital of Alaska?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Dacca",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What is the capital of Bangladesh?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Rangoon",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What is the capital of Burma?",
      "regexp": "(dhakk?a|dacc?a)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Santiago",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What is the capital of Chile?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Denver",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What is the capital of Colorado?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Tallahassee",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What is the capital of Florida?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "New Delhi",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What is the capital of India?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Jakarta",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What is the capital of Indonesia?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Topeka",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What is the capital of Kansas?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Augusta",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What is the capital of Maine?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Lincoln",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What is the capital of Nebraska",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Wellington",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What is the capital of New Zealand?",
      "regexp": "Lin?coln"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Olympia",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What is the capital of Washington state?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Charleston",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What is the capital of West Virginia?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Madison",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What is the capital of Wisconsin?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Harare",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What is the capital of Zimbabwe?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Abu Dhabi",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What is the capital of the United Arab Emirates?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Namibia",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What is the current name for south-west Africa?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Mt. #Logan#",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What is the highest mountain in Canada?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Sydney",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What is the largest city in Australia, in terms of population?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Shanghai",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What is the largest city in China?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Nicaragua",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What is the largest of the countries in Central America?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Rupee",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What is the monetary unit of India?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Ganges",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What is the most sacred river in India?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Arabic",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What is the official language of Egypt?",
      "regexp": "Gang(a|es)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Shannon",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What is the principal river of Ireland?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Texas",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What is the second largest of the United States?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Prince Edward Island",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What is the smallest Canadian province?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "#Vatican# City",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What is the smallest independent state in the world?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "El Salvador",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What is the smallest of the Central American countries?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Lhasa",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What is the world's highest city?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Bermuda",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What island has Hamilton as its capital?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Zanzibar",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What island is known as the Spice Island?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Ural",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What mountain range separates Europe from Asia?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "#Devil#'s Island",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What prison island was off the coast of French Guiana?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Amazon",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What river has the largest drainage basin?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Mersey",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What river is Liverpool on?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Mississippi",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What river is called \"Old Man River\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Yellow",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What river is known as China's Sorrow?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Nile",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What river is the Temple of Karnak near?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Adriatic",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What sea is between Italy and Yugoslavia?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Colombia",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What south American country has both a Pacific and Atlantic coastline?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Tennessee",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What state borders Alabama to the north?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "California",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What state is the Golden State?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "North Carolina",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What state was the home to Mayberry?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "star",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What symbol is on the flag of Vietnam?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Dinar",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What unit of currency will buy you dinner in Iraq, Jordan, Tunisia, and Yugoslavia?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Etna",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What volcano showers ash on Sicily?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Constantinople",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What's the former name of Istanbul?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Whitney",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "What's the highest mountain in the 48 contiguous U.S. states?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Peru",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Where are the Nazca Lines?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Egypt",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Where are the pyramids located?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Boston",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Where is Beacon Street?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "London",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Where is Euston Station?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Mt. Vernon, Virginia",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Where is George Washington buried?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Antarctica",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Where is Queen Maud Land located?",
      "regexp": "M(oun)?t.? ?Vernon"
    },
    {
      "answer": "London",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Where is Westminster Abbey located?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "London",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Where is the Admirality Arch?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Mecca",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Where is the Holy Kaaba?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Athens",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Where is the Parthenon located?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Philadelphia",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Where is the city of Brotherly Love?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Gibraltar",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Where were the Pillars of Hercules located?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Quebec",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Which Canadian province extends farthest north?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Belize",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Which Central American country extends furthest north?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Monaco",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Which European country has the highest population density?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Iceland",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Which European country has the lowest population density?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Waterford",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Which Irish city is famous for its crystal?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Boston",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Which U.S. city is known as Beantown?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Reno",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Which U.S. city is known as the Biggest Little City in the World?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Alaska",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Which U.S. state borders a Canadian territory?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Nevada",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Which U.S. state has the least rainfall?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Hawaii",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Which U.S. state receives the most rainfall?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Toledo",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Which capital is known as the Glass Capital of the World?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Calgary",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Which city has the largest rodeo in the world?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Detroit",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Which city is known as Motown?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Chicago",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Which city is known as the Windy City?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Oakland",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Which city is on the east side of San Francisco Bay?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Australia",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Which country administers Christmas Island?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Ecuador",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Which country are the Galapagos Islands part of?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Austria",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Which country borders Italy, Switzerland, West Germany, Czechoslovakia, Hungary, Yugoslavia, and Liechtenstein?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Korea",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Which country developed \"Tae-Kwan-Do\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Turkey",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Which country has Ankara as its capital?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Hungary",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Which country has Budapest as its capital?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "China",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Which country has the longest land border?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Spain",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Which country hosted the 1982 World Cup of soccer?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Japan",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Which country uses the \"yen\" for currency?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Afghanistan",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Which country would come first in an alphabetical list of countries?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "The #Philippine#s",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Which islands were named after Prince Philip of Spain?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Mexico",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Which mainland Latin American country is in neither South America nor Central America?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Minnesota",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Which of the 48 contiguous states extends farthest north?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Maine",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Which of the U.S. states borders only one other state?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Amazon",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Which river contains the most fresh water?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "California",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Which state has the most hospitals?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Michigan",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Which state is divided into two parts by a large lake?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Washington",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Which state is the Evergreen State?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "New Jersey",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Which state is the Garden State?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Michigan",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "Which state is the Wolverine State?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Cuba",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "With what country is Fidel Castro associated?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Monaco",
      "category": "Geography",
      "question": "With which country is Prince Rainier III identified?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Salt Lake City",
      "category": "Geogrpahy",
      "question": "Name the capital city of Utah.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Lithosphere",
      "category": "Geology",
      "question": "Earth's outer layer of surface soil or crust is called the .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "coal",
      "category": "Geology",
      "question": "Peat, lignite and bituminous are types of .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "shale",
      "category": "Geology",
      "question": "Slate is formed by the metamorphosis of .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "emerald",
      "category": "Geology",
      "question": "The green variety of beryl is called .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "lava",
      "category": "Geology",
      "question": "The molten material from a volcano is ?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "epicenter",
      "category": "Geology",
      "question": "The spot on the Earth's surface directly above an earthquake's focus is called the .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "amethyst",
      "category": "Geology",
      "question": "The violet variety of quartz is called .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "igneous",
      "category": "Geology",
      "question": "There are three types of rocks: metamorphic, sedimentary, and .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "stalagmites",
      "category": "Geology",
      "question": "These limestone deposits rise from the floor of caves.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "diamond",
      "category": "Geology",
      "question": "This is the hardest naturally occurring substance.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "permafrost",
      "category": "Geology",
      "question": "What name is used to describe permanently-frozen subsoil?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "chair",
      "category": "Hahaha",
      "question": "This normally has 4 legs and your butt is parked in it right now.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Haiti",
      "category": "Hirtory",
      "question": "Name the first black nation to gain freedom from European colonial rule.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "#Falkland#s Islands",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "Britain and Argentina fought over these islands in 1982.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Trudeau",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "Canadian Prime Minister: Pierre Elliott .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Yalta",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "Churchill, F.D. Roosvelt and Stalin met here in 1945.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "periods",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "Eras are divided into units called .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Spain",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "For what country did Columbus make his historic voyage?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Midway",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "Four Japanese carriers were destroyed in this battle.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Charlemagne",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "Frankish ruler Charles the Great is better known as .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Denmark",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "From what country did the U.S. buy the Virgin Islands?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Atlanta",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "General Sherman burned this city in 1864.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Turkey",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "Germany's WW I allies were Austria-Hungary, Bulgaria, and .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Romania",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "Germany's allies in WW II were Japan, Italy, Hungary, Bulgaria, Finland, Libya, and .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Richard #Nixon#",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "He allowed the bugging of the Democratic Committee headquarters.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Francisco #Coronado#",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "He discovered the Grand Canyon.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Archimedes",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "He is identified with the expression, \"Eureka\".",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Nero",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "He is said to have fiddled while Rome burned.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Jim Jones",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "He led 900 followers in a mass suicide in 1979.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Nero",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "He ordered the persecution of Christians in which Peter and Paul died.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "#Martin Luther King# Jr.",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "He received the Nobel Peace Prize in 1964 for his civil rights leadership.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Sir Winston #Churchill#",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "He said, \"I have nothing to offer but blood, tears, toil and sweat.\"",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Jack Ruby",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "He shot Lee Harvey Oswald.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Aristotle",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "He taught Alexander the Great.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "John Lennon",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "He was assassinated on Dec. 8, 1980 in New York City.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "John Fitzgerald #Kennedy#",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "He was assassinated on Nov. 22, 1963.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "General #Custer#",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "He was defeated at the Battle of Little Bighorn.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Julius Caesar",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "He was stabbed by Gaius Cassius Longinus.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Eli #Whitney#",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "He was the American inventor of the Cotton Gin.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Abraham #Lincoln#",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "He was the U.S. president during the Civil War.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Charles #Darwin#",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "His ship was the H.M.S. Beagle.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Alexander the Great",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "His wife was Roxana. His horse was Bacephalus. He was .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "LXIX",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "How do you write 69 in Roman numerals?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "three",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "How many astronauts manned each Apollo flight?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "forty three",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "How old was John F. Kennedy when he became president?",
      "regexp": "(three|3)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Pelee",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "In 1902 this volcano erupted, killing 30,000.",
      "regexp": "(forty[- ]three|43)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "India",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "In what country did \"Sepoy Mutiny\" occur?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Dallas",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "In which city was President Kennedy killed?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Babylon",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "In which city were the Hanging Gardens?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "China",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "In which country did the Boxer Rebellion take place?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Austria",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "In which country was Adolf Hitler born?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Egypt",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "In which country was the Rosetta Stone found?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Syria",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "Israel occupied the Golan Heights.  Whose territory was it?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Jordan",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "Israel occupied the West Bank.  It belonged to .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Idlewind",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "John F. Kennedy Airport in New York used to be called .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Ethiopia",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "Mussolini invaded this country in 1935.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Calypso",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "Name Jacques Cousteau's research ship.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Boston Tea Party",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "Name the incident in which tea was dumped into the harbour.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Gladiator",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "One who fought professionally in Roman arenas was a(n) .",
      "regexp": "Boston Tea[- ]Party"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Helen #Keller#",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "She overcame her handicaps to become a lecturer and a scholar.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Cleopatra",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "She was Queen of Egypt and mistress of Julius Caesar.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Joan of Arc",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "She was called \"The Maid of Orleans\".",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Jackie #Kennedy#",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "She was the first First Lady to be received privately by the Pope.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Golda #Meir#",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "She was the first woman premier of Israel.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Amelia #Earhart#",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "She was the first woman to fly the Atlantic solo.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Gertrude Caroline #Ederle#",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "She was the first woman to swim the English channel.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Annie Oakley",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "She was the greatest trick shot artist of all time.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Mother Teresa",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "She won the 1979 Nobel Peace Prize for her work among the poor.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Cuba",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "Spain ceded Florida to Britain in exchange for this territory.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Cuba",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "The \"Bay of Pigs\" fiasco took place in this country.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "fish",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "The Devonian Period is also known as the Age of .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Galileo",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "The Inquisition forced him to recant his belief in the Copernican Theory.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "aqueducts",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "The Romans built these to convey water.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Chicago",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "The St. Valentine's Day massacre took place in this city.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Laika",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "The first dog in space was named .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Communist Manifesto",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "The last line of this document is \"Working men of all countries, unite.\"",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Elliot Ness",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "This F.B.I agent headed the investigation of Al Capone.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Joan of Arc",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "This French peasant girl led the army to victories.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Inca",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "This Indian group ruled in early Peru.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Joseph #Goebbels#",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "This Nazi leader had his six children poisoned prior to his own death.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Marie Antoinette",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "This Queen of France was beheaded in 1793.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Marc Antony",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "This Roman killed himself after his defeat at Actium.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Sitting Bull",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "This Sioux Indian toured with Buffalo Bill's Wild West Show.",
      "regexp": "Anth?ony"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Hernando #Cortez#",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "This Spaniard conquered Mexico.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Henry #Kissinger#",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "This U.S. Secretary of State won the Nobel Peace Prize in 1973.",
      "regexp": "corte[sz]"
    },
    {
      "answer": "James #Garfield#",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "This U.S. president was fatally shot in 1881.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Brutus",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "This assassin of Julius Caesar was his friend.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Davy #Crockett#",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "This frontiersman and politician was killed at the Alamo.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Dunkirk",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "This is said to be history's greatest military evacuation.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Pearl Harbour",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "This military attack took place on Dec. 7, 1941.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Salvation Army",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "This organization was founded by William Booth.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Ku Klux Klan",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "This racist organization was formed in Tennessee in 1865.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Korean",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "This war began on June 25, 1950.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Louisiana Purchase",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "This was the largest real estate deal in U.S. history.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "holocaust",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "This word describes the Nazi annihilation of Jews.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "vinyl",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "Those big black CD's that you see at garage sales that people call \"albums\" are made of .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Canary Islands",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "Two 747's collided here in 1977.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Arthur",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "U.S. President, Chester Alan .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Hoover",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "U.S. President, Herbert C. .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Adams",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "U.S. President, John Quincy .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Coolidge",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "U.S. President: Calvin .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Susan B. #Anthony#",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "What American feminist went bust as a silver dollar?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Manchu",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "What Chinese dynasty was overthrown in 1911?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "The #Bronze# Age",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "What age preceded the Iron Age?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "A #wife#",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "What did President J. Buchanan not have?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "The first name \"#James#\"",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "What did presidents Madison, Monroe, Polk, and Garfield have in common?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "The #Pilgrim#s",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "What group landed in America in 1620?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "L",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "What is the Roman numeral for fifty?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Anastasia",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "What is the name of the Russian Czar's daughter who might-or might not-have survived the Russian revolution?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Vesuvius",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "What volcano destroyed Pompeii?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "guillotine",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "What was the instrument of execution during the \"Reign of Terror\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Academy",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "What was the name of Plato's school?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Enola Gay",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "What was the name of the B-29 used at Hiroshima to drop the bomb?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "British",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "What was the nationality of the prisoners in the \"Black hole of Calcutta\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Britain",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "What was the third country to get the \"bomb\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Davey Jones's Locker",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "What's the resting place of those buried at sea?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Truman",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "Which U.S. president said, \"The buck stops here\"?",
      "regexp": "(Dave?y Jones's? Locker)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Waterloo",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "Which military battle took place in 1815?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "The #Mongol#s",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "Which nation was led by Genghis Khan?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Jefferson",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "Which president was responsible for the Louisiana Purchase?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Margaret Thatcher",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "Who is \"The Iron Lady\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Santa Ana",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "Who led the attack on the Alamo?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Lady Godiva",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "Who rode naked through the streets of Coventry?",
      "regexp": "santa ann?a"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Julius #Caesar#",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "Who said \"Veni, vidi, vici\" (I came, I saw, I conquered)?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Marie Antoinette",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "Who said: \"Let them eat cake\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Marilyn Monroe",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "Who sang Happy Birthday to John F. Kennedy for his 45th?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Sir Anthony #Eden#",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "Who succeeded Churchill when he resigned in 1955?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Rasputin",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "Who was \"The Mad Monk\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Adams",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "Who was George Washington's vice-president?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Konrad #Adenauer#",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "Who was the first chancellor of West Germany after WW II?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Edwin \"Buzz\" #Aldrin#",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "Who was the second man to set foot on the moon?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "George Washington",
      "category": "History",
      "question": "Who was, \"First in war, first in peace and first in the hearts of his countrymen\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "lol",
      "category": "IRC",
      "question": "What three letters are overly used to indicate \"Laugh Out Loud\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "gas",
      "category": "Langauge",
      "question": "Many Meanings:  Fuel, vapor, flattulence, helium.  What is it?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "glasses",
      "category": "Language",
      "question": "Multiple Meanings:  Drinking utensils or sight-enhancers.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "clap",
      "category": "Language",
      "question": "Multiple Meanings:  Slamming your hands together quickly, or a venereal disease.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Coke",
      "category": "Language",
      "question": "Name the soda that is often confused with a drug.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "sentence",
      "category": "Language",
      "question": "Subject, verb and object are parts of a .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "aardvark",
      "category": "Language",
      "question": "This animal is found at the beginning of an (English) encyclopedia",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "cab",
      "category": "Language",
      "question": "What is the only English word formed by the first three letters of the alphabet?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "eat",
      "category": "Language",
      "question": "What three letter word means the same as \"to ingest\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "mistake",
      "category": "Languages",
      "question": "\"faux pas\" means .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "fat tuesday",
      "category": "Languages",
      "question": "Mardi Gras is French for .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "southern",
      "category": "Languages",
      "question": "The name Australia is derived from the Latin word \"australis\" which means .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "aquamarine",
      "category": "Languages",
      "question": "The name for this semi-precious stone comes from the Latin for \"sea water\"",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "man",
      "category": "Languages",
      "question": "What ONE word fits? hood; hole; date.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "down",
      "category": "Languages",
      "question": "What ONE word fits? stream; hill; pour.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "that's life",
      "category": "Languages",
      "question": "What does \"c'est la vie\" mean?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "saXOPhone",
      "category": "Languages",
      "question": "What word contains the combination of letters: \"xop\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "The #Diary of a Young Girl#",
      "category": "Literature",
      "question": "\"The Diary of Anne Frank\" was first published in English under what title?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Peter Pan",
      "category": "Literature",
      "question": "Captain Hook, Tiger Lily, and Tinker Bell are characters in what story?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Hat",
      "category": "Literature",
      "question": "Dr. Seuss wrote this book: The Cat in the .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "raven",
      "category": "Literature",
      "question": "Edgar Allen Poe wrote a famous poem about this animal.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Macbeth",
      "category": "Literature",
      "question": "From which Shakespeare play is this line taken: \"Double, double ... \"",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Romeo and Juliet",
      "category": "Literature",
      "question": "From which Shakespeare play is this line taken: \"Goodnight, goodnight! Parting is such sweet sorrow, That I should say goodnight till it be morrow.\"",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Hamlet",
      "category": "Literature",
      "question": "From which Shakespeare play is this line taken: \"To be or not to be?\"",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Romeo and Juliet",
      "category": "Literature",
      "question": "From which Shakespeare play is this line taken: \"What in a name? That which we call a rose, by any other name would smell as sweet.\"",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "fourteen",
      "category": "Literature",
      "question": "How many lines are in a sonnet?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "thirty seven",
      "category": "Literature",
      "question": "How many plays is Shakespeare generally credited with today?",
      "regexp": "(fourteen|14)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Macbeth",
      "category": "Literature",
      "question": "Name the Shakespeare play from this ultra short plot summary: Urged on by his wife, a man murders his king in order to take his place.",
      "regexp": "(thirty[- ]seven|37)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Semetary",
      "category": "Literature",
      "question": "Stephen King's: \"Pet \".",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Lot",
      "category": "Literature",
      "question": "Stephen King's: \"Salem's \".",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Zone",
      "category": "Literature",
      "question": "Stephen King's: \"The Dead \".",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Macbeth",
      "category": "Literature",
      "question": "This Shakespearean king was the actual king of Scotland for 17 years.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Anne Frank",
      "category": "Literature",
      "question": "This girl hid from the Nazis in Amsterdam.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Romeo and Juliet",
      "category": "Literature",
      "question": "What Shakespearean play features the line: A plague on both your houses?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Harper Valley",
      "category": "Literature",
      "question": "What did Jeannie C. Riley describe as \"a little Peyton Place\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Richard #Bachman#",
      "category": "Literature",
      "question": "What other name does Stephen King write under?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Popular Science",
      "category": "Literature",
      "question": "What publication was subtitled The What's New Magazine?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Jack",
      "category": "Literature",
      "question": "What was the name of Mother Goose's son?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Viva",
      "category": "Literature",
      "question": "What's Penthouse's sister publication for women?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Iliad",
      "category": "Litterature",
      "question": "Homer wrote this account of the Trojan War.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "White",
      "category": "Logic",
      "question": "You are in a room where all walls face south.  A bear walks by.  What color is it?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "ten",
      "category": "Mathematics",
      "question": "A U.S. dime is worth  cents.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "median",
      "category": "Mathematics",
      "question": "A line drawn from an angle of a triangle to the mid-point of the opposite side is a(n) .",
      "regexp": "(ten|10)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "equilateral",
      "category": "Mathematics",
      "question": "A triangle with three equal sides is called .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "isosceles",
      "category": "Mathematics",
      "question": "A triangle with two equal sides is called .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "reflex",
      "category": "Mathematics",
      "question": "An angle greater than 180 degrees and less than 360 degrees is a(n)  angle.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "obtuse",
      "category": "Mathematics",
      "question": "An angle greater than 90 degrees and less than 180 degrees is said to be .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "prime",
      "category": "Mathematics",
      "question": "An integer that is greater than 1 and is divisible only by itself and 1 is known as a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "thirty nine",
      "category": "Mathematics",
      "question": "Approximately how many inches are there in one meter?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "circle",
      "category": "Mathematics",
      "question": "Arc, radius, and sector are parts of a(n) .",
      "regexp": "(thirty[- ]nine|39)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Euclid",
      "category": "Mathematics",
      "question": "He is known as \"The Father of Geometry\".",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "eight",
      "category": "Mathematics",
      "question": "How many corners are there in a cube?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "forty five",
      "category": "Mathematics",
      "question": "How many nickles are there in 2.25?",
      "regexp": "(eight|8)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "circle",
      "category": "Mathematics",
      "question": "If you cut through a solid sphere what shape will the flat area be?",
      "regexp": "(forty[- ]five|45)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "The #binary# system",
      "category": "Mathematics",
      "question": "Name the number system which uses only the symbols 1 and 0.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "three hundred and sixty",
      "category": "Mathematics",
      "question": "The angles inside a square total  degrees.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "geometry",
      "category": "Mathematics",
      "question": "The mathematical study of properties of lines, angels, etc., is .",
      "regexp": "(three hundred (and |& )?sixty|360)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "volume",
      "category": "Mathematics",
      "question": "The space occupied by a body is called its .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "1",
      "category": "Mathematics",
      "question": "The square root of 1 is?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "supplementary",
      "category": "Mathematics",
      "question": "Two angles that total 180 degrees are called .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "square",
      "category": "Mathematics",
      "question": "What geometric shape has 4 equal sides?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "pediatrician",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "A baby doctor is a .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "osteopath",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "A bone specialist is a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "amnesia",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "A loss of memory is known as .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "laxative",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "A medicine that hastens the emptying of the bowels is called a .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "benign",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "A non-cancerous tumor is said to be .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "ligature",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "A thread used in surgery to tie a bleeding blood vessel is called a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "heart",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "Carditis, affects the .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "stethoscope",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "Doctors often have this instrument around their neck.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "scurvy",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "Due to a lack of vitamin C, sailors used to contract this disease.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "brain",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "Encephalitis affects the .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "stomach",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "Gastritis affects the .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "ear",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "Hammer, anvil, and stirrup are parts of the .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Edward #Jenner#",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "He discovered the process of vaccination for prevention of smallpox.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Liver",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "Hepatitis affects the .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "two hundred and six",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "How many bones are there in the human body?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "four",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "How many chambers does the human heart have?",
      "regexp": "(two hundred (and |& )?six|206)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "twelve",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "How many pints of blood does the average human have in his/her body?",
      "regexp": "(four|4)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "narcissism",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "In the field of psychiatry this term means self-love.",
      "regexp": "(twelve|12)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "pancreas",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "In what organ of the body is insulin produced?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "eye",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "In which organ is a clear watery solution known as the \"aqueous humor\" found?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "lung",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "In which organ is a pulmonary disease located?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "brain",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "In which organ is your \"hypothalmus\" located?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "polio",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "Infantile Paralysis is commonly known as .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "brain",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "Meningitis affects the .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "muscles",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "Myositis affects the .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "enamel",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "Name the hardest substance in the human body.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "aorta",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "Name the largest artery in the human body.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "liver",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "Name the largest gland in the human body.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "bones",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "Osteomyelitis affects the .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "abdomen",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "Peritonitis, affects the .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "artificial limbs",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "Prosthetics deals with the making of .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "foot",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "Tarsus, metatarsus, and phalanges are parts of a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "surgery",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "The branch of medicine dealing with curing by operative procedures is .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "iodine",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "The lack of this element in the diet is a cause of goitre.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "skin",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "The largest single organ of the human body is the .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "larynx",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "The medical name for the voice box is the .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "incisors",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "The teeth used for biting or cutting are known as .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "leeches",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "These animals were once used to bleed the sick.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "#tendon#s",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "These attach muscles to bones or cartilage.",
      "regexp": "leech(es)?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "geriatrics",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "This branch of medicine deals with old age and its diseases.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "leukemia",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "This disease consists of a purposeless, continual growth of white blood cells.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "appendix",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "This fingerlike projection is attached to the large intestine.",
      "regexp": "leuka?emia"
    },
    {
      "answer": "haemophilia",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "This is known as \"The Royal Disease\".",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "spleen",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "This large bean-shaped lymph gland can expand and contract as needed.",
      "regexp": "ha?emophilia"
    },
    {
      "answer": "iris",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "This membrane controls the amount of light entering the eye.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "gall bladder",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "This organ is a small pouch that stores bile.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "tapeworm",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "This parasite lives in the intestines of man and animals.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "pituitary",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "This small gland attached to the brain exerts a control over growth.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "bone",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "Ulna, radius, and clavicle are types of .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "German measles",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "What disease is also known as \"rubella\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "adrenaline",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "What hormone is produced by the adrenal glands?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "dermatologist",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "What is a skin specialist called?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "parasite",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "What is an organism called that lives on or in a host animal?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "eyesight",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "What is the biggest disqualifying factor for prospective astronauts?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "leukemia",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "What is the medical term for cancer of the blood?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "tibia",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "What is the name of the bone in the lower leg?",
      "regexp": "leuka?emia"
    },
    {
      "answer": "#lead# poisoning",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "What kind of poisoning is known as plumbism?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "big toe",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "What toe is the foot reflexology pressure point for the head?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "brain",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "Where do you find the medulla oblongata?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "ear",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "Where in the body is the tiniest human muscle?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "leprosy",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "Which disease is also known as \"Hansen's Disease\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "ear",
      "category": "Medicine",
      "question": "With what body part is otology involved?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "six",
      "category": "Meteorology",
      "question": "If the groundhog sees his shadow on Feb. 2, there will be how many more weeks of bad weather?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Chinook",
      "category": "Meteorology",
      "question": "This dry, warm wind flows eastward down the slopes of the Rocky Mountains.",
      "regexp": "(six|6)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Ernest",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Actor:  Borgnine.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Gene",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Actor:  Hackman.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Leonard",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Actor:  Nimoy.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Telly",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Actor:  Savalas.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Statue of Liberty",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "At the end of \"Planet of the Apes\" what protruded from the rocks?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Walter #Matthau#",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Barbara Streisand was the female lead in \"Hello, Dolly\".  Who was the male lead?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Hunchback of Notre Dame",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Charles Laughton played Quasimodo in this epic film.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Star",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Darth Vader was the villan in the movie, \" Wars\".",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Gentleman",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Film Title: An Officer and a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "451",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Film Title: Fahrenheit . (a number)",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Pompeii",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Film Title: The Last Days of . (a city)",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "20,000",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Film Title:  (a number) Leagues Under the Sea.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Gump",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Forrest  liked shrimp.",
      "regexp": "20[\\,.]?000"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Francis Ford #Coppola#",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "He directed \"The Godfather\".",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Stephen Spielberg",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "He directed the movie E.T.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Christopher Reeve",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "He played Superman in the 1978 movie version.",
      "regexp": "ste(ph|f)en spielberg"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Arnold #Schwarzenegger#",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "He starred in \"Conan the Barbarian\".",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Charlie #Chaplin#",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "He starred in, \"City Lights\".",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Joseph Merrick",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "He was known as the \"Elephant Man\".",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Darth Vader",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "He was the villain in \"Star Wars\".",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Rock #Hudson#",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "His films include: Giant, Written on the Wind, and A Farewell to Arms.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Kirk #Douglas#",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "His films include: Spartacus, The Vikings, and Ulysses.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "sawmill",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "In \"Gone With the Wind\", Scarlett regains her wealth by investing in what type of business?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "In 1975 Jack Nicholson won the best actor Oscar for his role in this film.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Claire #Danes#",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "In the 1996 version of \"Romeo and Juliet\", who played Juliet?",
      "regexp": "one flew over the cuckoo'?s nest"
    },
    {
      "answer": "The Good Ship #Lollipop#",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "In the film \"Bright Eyes\", Shirley Temple sang about this boat.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Rosemary's Baby",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "In this 1968 film the husband of an unsuspecting young wife becomes involved with a witch's coven.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Cinderella",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "In which Disney movie is the song \"So This Is Love\"?",
      "regexp": "Rosemary'?s Baby"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Beauty and the Beast",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Name the Disney cartoon in which the character \"Belle\" appears.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Clint #Eastwood#",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Name the actor who played the leading role in \"The Good, the Bad, and the Ugly\".",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Snow White",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Name the first full length color cartoon talking picture.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Oklahoma",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Name the musical film named after a state.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "48 Hours",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Nick Nolte and Eddie Murphy star in this 1982 film.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Clouseau",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Peter Sellers is best known for his role as Inspector .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Margot #Kidder#",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "She played Lois Lane in the 1978 film version of \"Superman\".",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Meryl #Streep#",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "She played a Polish refugee in \"Sophie's Choice\".",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Sissy #Spacek#",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "She played the lead role in \"Coal Miner's Daughter\".",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Marilyn Monroe",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "She starred in the 1952 film, \"Niagara\".",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Wizard of Oz",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "The first 18 minutes of this movie is black and white.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Fiddler On The Roof",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "The song \"Matchmaker, Matchmaker\" came from which musical play?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Jets",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "The two rival gangs in \"West Side Story\" were the Sharks and the .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "American Graffiti",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "This 1974 film started a run of nostalgia culminating in the TV series \"Happy Days\".",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "TRON",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "This Disney movie relies heavily on computer animation.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Demi Moore",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "This actress appeared in \"St. Elmo's Fire\", \"The Scarlett Letter\", and \"Striptease\".",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Zsa-Zsa #Gabor#",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "This actress was Miss Hungary of 1936.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Sound of Music",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "This film starring Julie Andrews and Christopher Plummer wont he best picture Oscar for 1965.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "West Side Story",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "This film starring Richard Beymer and Natalie Wood won the best picture Oscar for 1961.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Fantasia",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "This film was an ambitious concert sequence of cartoons by Walt Disney.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "King Kong",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "This is a classic film about a huge gorilla.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Supercalifragilisticexpialidocious",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "This magic word was in the movie, \"Mary Poppins\".",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Annie Hall",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "This movie directed by Woody Allen won the best picture Oscar in 1978.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "The #Grapes of Wrath#",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "This movie is about the migration of poor workers from the dust bowl to the Californian fruit valleys.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "The #Godfather#",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "This movie starring Marlon Brando won the best picture award in 1972.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Bwana Devil",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "This was the first 3-D film.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Steamboat Willie",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "This was the first cartoon talking picture.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "The #Empire Strikes Back#",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "This was the sequel to \"Star Wars\".",
      "regexp": "Steamboat Will(ie|y)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Return of the Jedi",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "This was the sequel to \"The Empire Strikes Back\".",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Dustin #Hoffman#",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "What actor appeared in all three of these films, Straw Dogs, Midnight Cowboy, and The Graduate?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Katherine #Hepburn#",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "What actress has received the most Oscar nominations?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Judy Garland",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "What actress's real name was Frances Gumm?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Honolulu",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "What city's police force did Charlie Chan work with?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Green",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "What color was Bullitt's car?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "#Siam# (Thailand)",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "What country was the setting for \"The King and I\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Hardy",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "What detective duo was featured in Mystery at Devil's Paw?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "A #Reel of Film#",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "What does the statue of Oscar stand on?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "King Kong",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "What famous animal character called \"Skull Island\" home?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "True Grit",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "What film did John Wayne win his only Oscar for?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Benjamin Franklin Pierce",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "What is Hawkeye's full name in M.A.S.H.?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Lisbon",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "What is the destination of the plane at the end of the film \"Casablanca\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Goldeneye",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "What is the name of Pearce Brosnan's first James Bond film?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Herbie",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "What is the name of the Volkswagen in the film, \"The Love Bug\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Thumper",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "What is the name of the rabbit in the film, \"Bambi\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Flower",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "What is the name of the skunk in the film, \"Bambi\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Monstro",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "What is the name of the whale that swallowed Pinocchio.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Greta #Garbo#",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "What is the stage name of Greta Gustafson?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Morning Star",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "What is the title of the 1996 sequel to \"Terms of Endearment\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Wookiee",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "What kind of creature was Chewbacca in \"Star Wars\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "The End",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "What two words are normally at the end of most movies?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Balboa",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "What was \"Rocky's\" last name?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Rosebud",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "What was Citizen Kane's dying word?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Gale",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "What was Dorothy's last name in \"The Wizard of Oz\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "The #Italian Stallion#",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "What was Rocky's nickname in the ring?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Obi-Wan Kenobi",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "What was Sir Alec Guinness's role in \"Star Wars\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Ordinary People",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "What was the first film directed by Robert Redford?",
      "regexp": "Obi(-|)?Wan Kenobi"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Twelve Oaks",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "What was the name of Ashley Wilkes' plantation in \"Gone With the Wind\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Millennium Falcon",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "What was the name of Han Solo's spaceship in \"Star Wars\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Yoda",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "What was the name of Luke's strange little advisor in \"The Empire Strikes Back\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "#Bates# Motel",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "What was the name of the motel in the film \"Psycho\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Austria",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "What was the setting for \"The Sound of Music\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Ryan O'Neil",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Which actor said, \"Love means never having to say you're sorry\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Bubba",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Which character in \"Forrest Gump\" loved shrimp?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Glinda",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Which character sang \"Come Out, Come Out, Wherever You Are\" in \"The Wizard of Oz\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Jiminy Cricket",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Which character sang, \"When you wish upon a star..\" in Disney's \"Pinocchio\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Abbott and Costello",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Which comedy duo did the famous, \"Who's on first?\" routine?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Earth",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Which planet was the \"Planet of the Apes\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Dick Van Dyke",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Who co-starred with Julie Andrews in \"Mary Poppins\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Ellen #Degeneres#",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Who hosted the 1997 Grammy Awards?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Shirley MacLaine",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Who is Warren Beatty's sister?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Speedy Gonzalez",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Who is the fastest mouse in all of Mexico?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Leslie Nielsen",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Who is the male lead in the \"Naked Gun\" movies?",
      "regexp": "speedy gonzale[sz]"
    },
    {
      "answer": "James Earl Jones",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Who is the voice of Darth Vadar?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Christopher #O'Donnell#",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Who played \"Robin\" to Val Kilmer's \"Batman\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Morgan Freeman",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Who played Brad Pitt's cop partner in the movie \"Seven\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Judy Garland",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Who played Dorothy in \"The Wizard of Oz\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Dana Carvey",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Who played Garth in \"Wayne's World\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Dean Martin",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Who played Matt Helm in the movies?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Vivien Leigh",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Who played Scarlette O'Hara in \"Gone With the Wind\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Margaret #Hamilton#",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Who played the 'Wicked Witch of the West' in \"The Wizard of Oz\"",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Humphrey Bogart",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Who played the role of Richard Blaine in Casablanca?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Sean Connery",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Who plays the character of the only escapee from Alcatraz in the movie \"The Rock\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Harrison Ford",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Who portrayed Han Solo in \"Star Wars\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Charlton Heston",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Who portrayed Moses in \"The Ten Commandments\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Orson Welles",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Who produced, directed and starred in \"Citizen Kane\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Christian Slater",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Who starred with John Travolta in the movie \"Broken Arrow\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "R2D2",
      "category": "Movie Trivia",
      "question": "Who was C3PO's sidekick in \"Star Wars\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "The #Chiffons#",
      "category": "Music",
      "question": "\"He's So Fine\", \"One Fine Day\" and \"A Love So Fine\" where hits for what fine group?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Three Dog Night",
      "category": "Music",
      "question": "\"Joy to the World\" was a hit in 1971 for what band with three lead vocalists?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Happy Birthday",
      "category": "Music",
      "question": "Besides \"Auld Lang Syne\" and \"For He's a Jolly Good Fellow\", what is the most frequently sung song in English?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Sha Na Na",
      "category": "Music",
      "question": "Fifties rock \"n\" roll was revived by what greased hair, T-shirted, TV frequenting group?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "#balls#!",
      "category": "Music",
      "question": "Jerry Lee Lewis had Great  Of Fire.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "The #Grateful Dead#",
      "category": "Music",
      "question": "Name Jerry Garcia's long lived group.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Tommy",
      "category": "Music",
      "question": "The Who's rock musical stars Elton John.  It's called .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Olivia Newton-John",
      "category": "Music",
      "question": "This female artist enjoyed sucess on both popular and country & western stations with such tunes as \"Let Me Be There\" and \"Have You Never Been Mellow.\"",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "A Hard Day's Night",
      "category": "Music",
      "question": "This was the Beatle's first film.",
      "regexp": "Olivia Newton[- ]John"
    },
    {
      "answer": "The #Everly Brothers#",
      "category": "Music",
      "question": "Through 1963 this duo's total record sales exceeded 18 million with successes including \"Cathy's Clown\" and \"Wake Up Little Suzie\".",
      "regexp": "(A )?Hard Day'?s Night"
    },
    {
      "answer": "A #Whiter Shade of Pale#",
      "category": "Music",
      "question": "What Procol Harem tune was based on the Bach cantata \"Sleepers Awake\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "The #Blues Brothers#",
      "category": "Music",
      "question": "What band recorded the 1978 hit album: \"Briefcase Full of Blues\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Nashville",
      "category": "Music",
      "question": "What city is also known as Music City, U.S.A.?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Willie #Nelson#",
      "category": "Music",
      "question": "What country singer/songwriter (and sometimes actor) is known as \"the country outlaw\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Michael Jackson",
      "category": "Music",
      "question": "What entertainer is allowing one of his songs to be used in a government campaign to beat drunk driving?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Ludwig van #Beethoven#",
      "category": "Music",
      "question": "What famous classical composer continued to compose great music after becoming deaf?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Elvis Presley",
      "category": "Music",
      "question": "What famous singer was known to give automobiles to complete strangers?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Kiss",
      "category": "Music",
      "question": "What group refused to have their pictures taken while they were not in their makeup?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "The #Ronettes#",
      "category": "Music",
      "question": "What group's biggest-ever hit was Be My Baby?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "American Pie",
      "category": "Music",
      "question": "What song by Don McLean talks about the day Buddy Holly died?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Think",
      "category": "Music",
      "question": "What song did Aretha Franklin sing in \"The Blues Brothers\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Priscilla",
      "category": "Music",
      "question": "What was Elvis Presley's wife's name?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Hey Jude",
      "category": "Music",
      "question": "What was The Beatles' biggest hit single?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Lucille",
      "category": "Music",
      "question": "What's the name of B.B. King's guitar?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Gus",
      "category": "Music",
      "question": "Which of Paul Simon's musical characters was told to hop on the bus?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Leo #Fender#",
      "category": "Music",
      "question": "Who invented the electrical bass?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Debby Reynolds",
      "category": "Music",
      "question": "Who recorded the 1957 hit \"Tammy\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Iron Butterfly",
      "category": "Music",
      "question": "Who recorded the lengthy song: \"In-A-Gadda-Da-Vida\" in 1969?",
      "regexp": "Debb(ie|y) Reynolds"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Peter Gabriel",
      "category": "Music",
      "question": "Who was the first singer in Genesis?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Gene #Autry#'s",
      "category": "Music",
      "question": "Whose theme song was Back In The Saddle Again?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "trident",
      "category": "Mythology",
      "question": "The sea gods had a three-pronged spear called a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Olympus",
      "category": "Mythology",
      "question": "This Greek mountain was known as the home of the gods.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "vampire",
      "category": "Mythology",
      "question": "What has no reflection, no shadow, and can't stand the smell of garlic?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Valhalla",
      "category": "Mythology",
      "question": "What's heaven to fallen Norse warriors?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Sherwood Forest",
      "category": "Mythology",
      "question": "Where did Robin Hood supposedly live?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Atlantis",
      "category": "Mythology",
      "question": "Which ancient continent is said to be submerged?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "brachiosaurus",
      "category": "Natural History",
      "question": "Name the largest of the dinosaurs.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "fossils",
      "category": "Natural History",
      "question": "The remains of prehistoric organisms that have been preserved in rocks are called .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "wind",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "A \"sirocco\" refers to a type of .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "#doldrum#s",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "A calm ocean region near the equator.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "atoll",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "A coral island consisting of a ring of rock enclosing a central lagoon is a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "tsunami",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "A great wave resulting from an earthquakes is called a (an) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "band",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "A group of gorillas is known as a .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "troop",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "A group of kangaroos is known as a .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "geyser",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "A hot spring which shoots steam into the air is a .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "dromedary",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "A one-humped camel is called a .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "symbiosis",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "A relationship between two different types of organism which live together for their mutual benefit.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "turtle",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "A terrapin is a type of .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "feathers",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "An animal is a bird if it has .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "gills",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "An animal is a fish if it has .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "flower",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "Corolla, filament and stigma are parts of a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "mangroves",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "Dense sea-water swamps along coasts of hot countries are called .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "bray",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "Dogs bark.  What do donkeys do?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "elephant",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "Excluding man, what is the longest-lived land mammal?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "fish",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "Fandible, lateral line, and dorsal fin are parts of a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "sperm whale",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "From what animal is \"ambergis\" obtained?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "ten",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "How man legs does a crab have?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "four",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "How many teats does a cow have?",
      "regexp": "(ten|10)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "ten",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "How many tentacles does a squid have?",
      "regexp": "(four|4)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "moth",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "Imperial, Buck, and Luna are types of .",
      "regexp": "(ten|10)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "fish",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "Knife, Clown, and Pencil are types of .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "flax",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "Linseed oil is obtained from the seed of which plant?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "insect",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "Maxillary palps, abdomen, and metathorax are parts of a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "antelope",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "Name the fastest land animal over a prolonged distance (1,000 yd. plus)",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "St. #Bernard#",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "Name the heaviest breed of domestic dog.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "condor",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "Name the heaviest flying bird of prey.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "ostrich",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "Name the largest living bird.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "albatross",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "Name the largest web-footed bird.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "cobra",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "Name the longest venomous snake.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "yak",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "Name the mammal living at the highest altitude.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "black widow",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "Name the most venomous spider.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "opossum",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "Name the only native North American marsupial.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "sloth",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "Name the slowest moving land mammal.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "chihuahua",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "Name the smallest breed of dog.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "dingo",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "Name the wild dogs of Australia.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "wood",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "Paper is made from the pulp of .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "amphibians",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "Snakes are reptiles.  What are frogs?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "hibernation",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "Some animals spend the winter in a sleep-like state known as .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "rattlesnake",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "The \"canebrake\", \"timber\" and \"pygmy\" are types of what?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "shark",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "The fins of which fish are made into a soup?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "larva",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "The four stages in the life-cycle of an insect are: egg, adult, pupa, and .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "eucalyptus",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "The koala bear eats the leaves from this tree.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "barnacles",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "These marine crustaceans often attach themselves to the hulls of ships.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "crocodile",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "This African animal kills the most people.",
      "regexp": "barnacles?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "armadillo",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "This animal is armed with bony plates and rolls up into a ball if frightened.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "mongoose",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "This animal is kept as a house pet to kill cobras.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "horse",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "This animal is normally measured in \"hands\".",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "donkey",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "This animal is the symbol of the U.S. Democratic Party.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "elephant",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "This animal is the symbol of the U.S. Republican Party.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "cardinal",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "This animal's name is the same as that given to a high church official.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "abalone",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "This animal's shell is used to make attractive jewelry.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "cuckoo",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "This bird lays its eggs in the nests of other birds.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "moose",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "This is the largest of the deer family.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "plankton",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "This is the main food of the blue whale.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "elephant",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "This is the only mammal with four knees.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "beetle",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "This order of insects contains the most species.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "coral",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "This organic gem is a deep red secretion from a marine animal.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "ferret",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "This small animal is trained to hunt rats and rabbits.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "rhinoceros",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "This two ton animal can gallop at over 50 miles an hour.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "mandrill",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "This ugly creature has patches of red on his rear-end.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "ivory",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "Walrus tusks are made of .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "marsupials",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "What are the pouched animals called?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "penguin",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "What bird is an excellent swimmer, but can't fly?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "fat",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "What does a camel store in its hump?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "sailfish",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "What fish is the fastest?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "exaltation",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "What is a group of larks called?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "muster",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "What is a group of peacocks called?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "pod",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "What is a group of whales called?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "gander",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "What is a male goose called?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "cob",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "What is a male swan called?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "boar",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "What is a male swine called?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "gosling",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "What is a young goose called?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "cygnet",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "What is a young swan called?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "gelding",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "What is an emasculated stallion called?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "panther",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "What is another term for a black leopard?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "hair",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "What is the horn of a rhinoceros made of?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "chow",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "What is the only dog that doesn't have a pink tongue?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "python",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "What is the world's longest snake?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "antelope",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "What large herbivore sleeps only one hour a night?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "heifer",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "What name is given to a female calf?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "poppy",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "What plant is opium derived from?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "geese",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "What travels in gaggles?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "marsupial",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "What type of animal is a wallaby?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "ant",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "What type of animal lives in a formicary?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "vixen",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "What word is used for a female fox?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "ewe",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "What word is used for a female sheep?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "jack",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "What word is used for a male ass? (Other than that the word used for that #*^*&%@! ex-boyfriend.)",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "buck",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "What word is used for a male deer?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "drake",
      "category": "Nature",
      "question": "What word is used for a male duck?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "acorns",
      "category": "Neture",
      "question": "What do oak trees grow from?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "#bird#s",
      "category": "Not Telling ;-)",
      "question": "What would be kept in an \"aviary\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "On the #moon#",
      "category": "Not Telling ;-)",
      "question": "Where is the Ocean of Storms located?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Bob Dylan",
      "category": "Not Telling ;-)",
      "question": "Who is Robert Zimmermann?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "stars",
      "category": "Not Telling ;-P",
      "question": "What are white dwarfs and red giants?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "gems",
      "category": "Not telling ;-P",
      "question": "What are these: chrysolite, beryl, jasper, and tourmaline?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "hill",
      "category": "Nursery Rhymes",
      "question": "Jack and Jill went up a  to fetch a pail of water?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "goose",
      "category": "Nursery Rhymes",
      "question": "Name the nursery rhyme mother whos last name is that of a bird?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "kinetic",
      "category": "Physics",
      "question": "The energy which a body possesses by virtue of its motion is called .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "fulcrum",
      "category": "Physics",
      "question": "The pivot point of a lever is called the .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "evaporation",
      "category": "Physics",
      "question": "The process of water changing to water vapor is known as .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "acceleration",
      "category": "Physics",
      "question": "The rate of change of velocity is known as .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "violet",
      "category": "Physics",
      "question": "The visible spectrum of light ranges from red to .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "false",
      "category": "Physics",
      "question": "True Or False: Contrary to popular belief, a lightbulb actually absorbs darkness?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "3",
      "category": "Physics",
      "question": "Two 1.5 volt batteries, when connected in series, produces _ volts.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "zero",
      "category": "Physics",
      "question": "Water freezes at _ degrees Celcius.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "thirty two",
      "category": "Physics",
      "question": "Water freezes at  degrees Fahrenheit.",
      "regexp": "(zero|0)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "radioactivity",
      "category": "Physics",
      "question": "What is measured by a Geiger counter?",
      "regexp": "(thirty[- ]two|32)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "refraction",
      "category": "Physics",
      "question": "When light waves pass from one medium into another they change direction.  This is called .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "distance",
      "category": "Physics",
      "question": "Work done, equals force multiplied by .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "The Organization of Petroleum Exporting Countries",
      "category": "Politics",
      "question": "For what does O.P.E.C. stand?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Francios #Mitterrand#",
      "category": "Politics",
      "question": "He was elected President of France, in 1981.",
      "regexp": "Organi[sz]ation of Petroleum Exporting Countries"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Wyman",
      "category": "Politics",
      "question": "Name Ronald Reagan's first wife.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Wilson",
      "category": "Presidents",
      "question": "U.S. President, Woodrow .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Mississippi",
      "category": "Quick! Quick!",
      "question": "How is the state of Mississippi spelled?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "CD",
      "category": "Quick! Quick!",
      "question": "Name the circular plastic media you put in a CD-ROM drive.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "x",
      "category": "Quick! Quick!",
      "question": "On a standard computer keyboard, this is the letter just to the right of Z.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "space",
      "category": "Quick! Quick!",
      "question": "The longest key on your keyboard is the  bar.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "summer",
      "category": "Quick! Quick!",
      "question": "The season  comes right after Spring.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "sixty",
      "category": "Quick! Quick!",
      "question": "There are  seconds in a minute.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "electricity",
      "category": "Quick! Quick!",
      "question": "This is required to make all electric things work?",
      "regexp": "(sixty|60)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "blue",
      "category": "Quick! Quick!",
      "question": "What color is a blue crayon?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "green",
      "category": "Quick! Quick!",
      "question": "What color is a green crayon?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "red",
      "category": "Quick! Quick!",
      "question": "What color is a red crayon?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "microsoft",
      "category": "Quick! Quick!",
      "question": "What company makes Microsoft Windows 2000?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "radar",
      "category": "Quick! Quick!",
      "question": "Whats radar spelled backwards?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "USA",
      "category": "Quick! Quick!",
      "question": "Whats the abbreviation for United States of America?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "computer",
      "category": "Quick! Where's my mirror? ;-",
      "question": "When spelled backwards, the word \"retupmoc\" becomes what?",
      "regexp": "U.?S.?A.?"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Moonies",
      "category": "Religion",
      "question": "Followers of the Unification Church are called .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Moses",
      "category": "Religion",
      "question": "He led the Israelites out of Egypt.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Saul",
      "category": "Religion",
      "question": "He was the first King of the Hebrews.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "David",
      "category": "Religion",
      "question": "He was the second King of Israel.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "December",
      "category": "Religion",
      "question": "In what month is Christmas observed?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Yom Kippur",
      "category": "Religion",
      "question": "Name the holiest day in the Jewish calendar.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Sinai",
      "category": "Religion",
      "question": "On which mountain did Moses receive the Ten Commandments?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Jerusalem",
      "category": "Religion",
      "question": "Which city is sacred to Jews, Christians, and Muslims?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Joseph #Smith#",
      "category": "Religion",
      "question": "Who founded Mormonism?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Jim Jones",
      "category": "Religion",
      "question": "Who founded the People's Temple Commune?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "#erlenmeyer# flask",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "A flat-bottomed conical laboratory flask with a narrow neck is called a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "skulls",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "A phrenologist reads .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "focus",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "A point to which rays of light converge is called a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "#petri# dish",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "A shallow dish with a cover, used for science specimens is a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "aspirin",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "Acetylsalicylic acid is more commonly known as .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "biology",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "Botany and Zoology combined make up the science of .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "photosynthesis",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "By what chemical process do plants manufacture food?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "LSD",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "By what name is Lysergic acid diethylamide better known?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "whales",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "Cetology is the study of .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "parallel",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "Circuits can be wired in series or in .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "bacteria",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "Cocci, Spirilla, and Streptococci are types of .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "DNA",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "Deoxyribonucleic acid is better known as .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "skin",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "Dermatitis affects the .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "leaf",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "Epidermal cells, palisade cells, and veins are parts of a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "anti-freeze",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "Ethylene glycol is frequently used in automobiles.. How?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "lightning",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "Forked, Sheet, and Ball are types of .",
      "regexp": "anti[- ]?freeze"
    },
    {
      "answer": "hydroponics",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "Growing plants in liquids rather than soil is known as .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Karl Freidrich #Benz#",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "He designed the first feasible automobile with an internal combustion engine.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Benjamin Franklin",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "He invented \"bifocal\" lenses for eyeglasses.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Charles #Darwin#",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "He is known for his theory of \"Evolution\".",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Enrico #Marconi#",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "He transmitted radio signals across the Atlantic in 1901.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Alfred #Kinsey#",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "He wrote \"Sexual Behaviour in the Human Male\" in 1948.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "fifteen",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "How many degrees does the earth rotate each hour?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "France",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "In which country was the match invented?",
      "regexp": "(fifteen|15)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "laughing gas",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "Nitrous oxide is better known as .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "cell",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "Nuclear membrane, cytoplasm, and nucleus are parts of a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "tooth",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "Pulp, crown, and root are parts of a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "tonic water",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "Quinine is added to water to make .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "sonar",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "Sound Navigation Ranging is better known as .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "temperature",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "The Kelvin scale is used to measure .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "tungsten",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "The filament of a regular light bulb is usually made of .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "protractor",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "The instrument used in geometry to measure angles is a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Salyut",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "The name for the Russian equivalent of Skylab is .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Columbia",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "The second space shuttle was named .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "spring",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "The vernal equinox is the beginning of .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Ivan #Pavlov#",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "This Russian scientist used dogs to study conditioned reflexes.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "helicopter",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "This is like an airplane but has its propeller on top instead.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Braille",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "This is the reading system used by the blind.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "ballistics",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "This science deals with the motion of projectiles.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "reverse",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "To make a car go backwards you have to put it in what gear?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "asteroids",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "What are these: Ceres, Juno, Iris, and Flora?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "aerodynamics",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "What branch of science studies the motion of air and the forces acting on objects in air?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "fountain pen",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "What did Lewis E. Waterman invent in 1884?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "The earth's crust",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "What does the \"lithosphere\" refer to?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "intelligence",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "What does the Binet test measure?",
      "regexp": "Earth'?s crust"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Alfred Nobel",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "Who invented dynamite?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Gregor #Mendel#",
      "category": "Science",
      "question": "Who is known as the father of genetics?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "brass",
      "category": "Similes",
      "question": "As bold as .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "whistle",
      "category": "Similes",
      "question": "As clean as a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "bell",
      "category": "Similes",
      "question": "As clear as a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "button",
      "category": "Similes",
      "question": "As cute as a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "pie",
      "category": "Similes",
      "question": "As easy as .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "fiddle",
      "category": "Similes",
      "question": "As fit as a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "gold",
      "category": "Similes",
      "question": "As good as .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "swan",
      "category": "Similes",
      "question": "As graceful as a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "life",
      "category": "Similes",
      "question": "As large as .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "thunder",
      "category": "Similes",
      "question": "As loud as .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "ghost",
      "category": "Similes",
      "question": "As pale as a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "punch",
      "category": "Similes",
      "question": "As pleased as .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "picture",
      "category": "Similes",
      "question": "As pretty as a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "peacock",
      "category": "Similes",
      "question": "As proud as a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "mouse",
      "category": "Similes",
      "question": "As quiet as a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "dog",
      "category": "Similes",
      "question": "As sick as a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "fox",
      "category": "Similes",
      "question": "As sly as a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "whip",
      "category": "Similes",
      "question": "As smart as a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "daisy",
      "category": "Similes",
      "question": "Fresh as a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Orioles",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Baseball: The Baltimore .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Bluejays",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Baseball: The Toronto .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Celtics",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Basketball: The Boston .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Nuggets",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Basketball: The Denver .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Lakers",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Basketball: The Los Angeles .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Knicks",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Basketball: The New York .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Supersonics",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Basketball: The Seattle .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Jazz",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Basketball: The Utah .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Colts",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Football: The Baltimore .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Bills",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Football: The Buffalo .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Bengals",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Football: The Cincinnati .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Browns",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Football: The Cleveland .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Cowboys",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Football: The Dallas .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Broncos",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Football: The Denver .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Dolphins",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Football: The Miami .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Vikings",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Football: The Minnesota .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Saints",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Football: The New Orleans .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Seahawks",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Football: The Seattle .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Wayne #Gretzky#",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "He holds the NHL record for the most goals scored during the regular season.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "He was the NBA, MVP in 1976, 77, and 80.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Bruins",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Hockey: The Boston .",
      "regexp": "Kareem Abdul[- ]?Jabbar"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Sabres",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Hockey: The Buffalo .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Flames",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Hockey: The Calgary .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Blackhawks",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Hockey: The Chicago .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Red Wings",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Hockey: The Detroit .",
      "regexp": "black ?hawks"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Oilers",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Hockey: The Edmonton .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Kings",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Hockey: The Los Angeles .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Canadians",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Hockey: The Montreal .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Penguins",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Hockey: The Pittsburgh .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Blues",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Hockey: The St. Louis .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Maple Leafs",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Hockey: The Toronto .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Canucks",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Hockey: The Vancouver .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "ten",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "How many feet high is a basketball net?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "six",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "How many games must you win to win a normal set in tennis?",
      "regexp": "(ten|10)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "five",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "How many minutes is a major penalty in hockey?",
      "regexp": "(six|6)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "twenty",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "How many minutes is each period of hockey?",
      "regexp": "(five|5)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "eleven",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "How many players are there on a soccer team?",
      "regexp": "(twenty|20)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "seven",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "How many players are there on a water polo team?",
      "regexp": "(eleven|11)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "eleven",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "How many players make up a field hockey team?",
      "regexp": "(seven|7)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "two",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "How many points are awarded for a safety touch in football?",
      "regexp": "(eleven|11)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "one",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "How many referees work a soccer game?",
      "regexp": "(two|2)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "four",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "How many seams are there on a football? (American)",
      "regexp": "(one|1)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "five",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "How many sides does a home-plate have?",
      "regexp": "(four|4)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "fifteen",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "In pro football a \"sudden death\" period lasts how many minutes long?",
      "regexp": "(five|5)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "three hundred",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "In ten-pin bowling, how many points does a perfect game consist of?",
      "regexp": "(fifteen|15)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "volleyball",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "In this team sport each player gets a chance to play every position.",
      "regexp": "(three hundred|300)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "American #football#",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "In what sport is the Heisman trophy awarded?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Dallas",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "In which city is the Cotton Bowl played?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Toronto",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "In which city is the Hockey Hall of Fame located?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "hockey",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "In which game or sport is a \"Zamboni\" used?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "golf",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "In which sport is a \"hole-in-one\" possible?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "sailing",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "In which sport is the America's Cup awarded?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "baseball",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "In which sport is the Cy Young Trophy awarded?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "tennis",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "In which sport is the Davis Cup awarded?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "tennis",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "In which sport is the term \"love\" used?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "football",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "In which sport is the term \"wishbone\" used?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "surfing",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "In which sport is the term, \"Hang ten\" used?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "hockey",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "In which sport would you find the \"slapshot\".",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "The #Lady Byng# Trophy",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Name the hockey trophy awarded to the player demonstrating the best sportsmanship.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "grass",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "On what type of surface are the tennis matches at Wimbledon played?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Billie Jean King",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "She was \"Sports Illustrated's\" first female \"Sportsman of the Year\".",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Cosmos",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Soccer: The New York .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Montreal",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "The 1976 Summer Olympics were held in this city.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "kendo",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "The Japanese martial art of fencing is called .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "caddie",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "The person who carries the golfer's clubs is called a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "#hash# marks",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "The white marks intersecting each five yard line are called .",
      "regexp": "cadd(ie|y)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "Grey Cup",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "This is the most coveted trophy in Candian football.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "hockey",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "This sport allows substitutions without a stoppage in play.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "baseball",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "This sport is called the \"American pastime\".",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "New York #Mets#",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "This team won their first World Series in 1969.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "sumo",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "This traditional Japanese wrestling sport takes place in a circular ring.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "eagle",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Two under par on a hole of golf is called a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "moguls",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "What are large snow bumps known as in skiing terms?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "baton",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "What do runners pass to each other in a relay race?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Earned Run Average",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "What do the letters ERA mean in baseball?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Technical Knock Out",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "What does TKO stand for?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "OJ #Simpson#",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "What football player rushed for 2,003 yards in 1973?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "earthball",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "What game features the largest ball?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "turnover",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "What is it called when a football team loses possession of the ball due to a misplay?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "super heavyweight",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "What is the heaviest class of weight-lifting?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "one",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "What number wood is a driver in golf?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "basketball",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "What sport do the Harlem Globetrotters play?",
      "regexp": "(one|1)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "rugby",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "What sport has a hooker in a scrum?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "skiing",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "What sport would you helicopter to the Bugaboos for?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Stanley Cup",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "What trophy is awarded to the winner of the NHL play-offs?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "bicycles",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "What vehicles are involved in the \"Tour de France\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Night Train",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "What was football player Dick Lane's nickname?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Bulldogs",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "What's the nickname of the University of Georgia football team?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "#Flushing Meadows#, NY",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Where are the U.S. Tennis Open Championships held?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Minnesota #Vikings#",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Which NFL team's defensive unit was nicknamed \"The Purple People Eaters\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Italy",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Which country won the World Cup of Soccer in 1982.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Denver #Broncos#",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Which football team was nicknamed the \"Orange Crush\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "goalkeeper",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Which is the only position in soccer allowed to handle the ball?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "centre",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Which position is usually played by the tallest member on a basketball team?",
      "regexp": "(goalie|goalkeeper)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "skiing",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Which sport has a movement called a \"telemark\"?",
      "regexp": "cent(er|re)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "curling",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Which sport uses stones and brooms?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "butterfly",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Which swimming stroke is named after an insect?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Babe Ruth",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Who was known as the \"Sultan of Swat\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Martina Navratilova",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Who was the 1978 Wimbledon Women's Singles champ?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Maurice #Richard# <-- pronounced \"Reeee-shard\"",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Who was the first NHL player to score 50 goals in one season?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Don #Budge#",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "Who was the first to win the grand slam of tennis?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "tennis",
      "category": "Sport",
      "question": "With which sport is Chris Evert Lloyd identified?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "upside down",
      "category": "Stand on your heads.... NOW! ;-)",
      "question": "When read upside down, what does the term \"umop apisdn\" signify?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "blind",
      "category": "Stupid things to do ;-)",
      "question": "If you look at the sun long enough, you go .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "beach",
      "category": "Summertime",
      "question": "This is the sandy area nearest the ocean.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Impossible Mission Forces",
      "category": "TV Trivia",
      "question": "What did TVs IMF stand for?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "American Bandstand",
      "category": "TV Trivia",
      "question": "What was the first network series devoted entirely to rock and roll?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Waite",
      "category": "TV Trivia",
      "question": "Who was Carl in Five Easy Pieces before going to Walton's Mountain?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Walt Disney",
      "category": "TV Trivia",
      "question": "Who was Chief Marshall of the Mickey Mouse Club?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "sinker",
      "category": "Triplets",
      "question": "Hook, line and .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Coca Cola",
      "category": "Trivia",
      "question": "\"7X\" was used to refer to the secret ingredient of which drink?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "football",
      "category": "Trivia",
      "question": "A \"pigskin\" is another name for a(n) .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "twelve",
      "category": "Trivia",
      "question": "A can of Pepsi holds  fluid ounces.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "twelve",
      "category": "Trivia",
      "question": "A foot-long ruler is  inches long.",
      "regexp": "(twelve|12)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "shave",
      "category": "Trivia",
      "question": "Most men do this each morning, using a razor.",
      "regexp": "(twelve|12)"
    },
    {
      "answer": "left",
      "category": "Trivia",
      "question": "Most people wear a watch on their  wrist.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "wiper",
      "category": "Trivia",
      "question": "Name the implement that removes water from your windshield on your car?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "green",
      "category": "Trivia",
      "question": "Traffic Trivia:  Red means stop,  means go.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Texas",
      "category": "Trivia",
      "question": "What US state has the Worlds Champion Chili Cookoff every year?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "honey",
      "category": "Trivia",
      "question": "What bit of Bobby Goldsboro syrup focused on a dying young wife?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "a #bow#",
      "category": "Trivia",
      "question": "What did Sally Rogers always wear in her hair?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "eggs",
      "category": "Trivia",
      "question": "What does the typical American eat 263 of each year? not pizza!!",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Let's #Make A Deal#",
      "category": "Trivia",
      "question": "What game show had people dressed up funny?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "A #tastebud#",
      "category": "Trivia",
      "question": "What is Grimace of the McDonald's characters?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "whale",
      "category": "Trivia",
      "question": "What was Simple Simon fishing for in his mother's pail?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Speedy",
      "category": "Trivia",
      "question": "What was the name of the Akla-Seltzer boy?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Nipper",
      "category": "Trivia",
      "question": "What was the name of the dog in RCA Victor's trademark?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "312",
      "category": "Trivia",
      "question": "What's the telephone area code for Chicago?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Doodyville",
      "category": "Trivia",
      "question": "Where did Howdy Doody live?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "The #Smithsonian# Institute",
      "category": "Trivia",
      "question": "Where were Archie and Edith Bunker's chairs enshrined?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Don #Rickles#",
      "category": "Trivia",
      "question": "Who is also known as Mr. Warmth?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "Dick #Clark#",
      "category": "Trivia",
      "question": "Who is known as \"the world's oldest teenager\"?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "chain",
      "category": "Word Asssociation",
      "question": "Ball and .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "quiet",
      "category": "Word Asssociation",
      "question": "Peace and .",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "cat",
      "category": "Word Asssociation",
      "question": "Which word is related to these three: nap, walk, call?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "finger",
      "category": "Word Asssociation",
      "question": "Which word is related to these three: painting, bowl, nail?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "cheese",
      "category": "Word Asssociation",
      "question": "Which word is related to these three: rat, blue, cottage?",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "FORt",
      "category": "Words containing 'for'",
      "question": "A castle or enclosed place.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "perFORate",
      "category": "Words containing 'for'",
      "question": "Make holes through something.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "FORest",
      "category": "Words containing 'for'",
      "question": "Many trees.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "FORgive",
      "category": "Words containing 'for'",
      "question": "Pardon.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {
      "answer": "tenderloin",
      "category": "Words containing 'ten'",
      "question": "A choice cut of meat.",
      "regexp": null
    },
    {"question": "Charmeleon evolves into Charizard to fight which pokemon?", "answer": "Aerodactyl"},
    {"question": "Ash Ketchum wins the 'Pokemon Race' with which Pokemon?", "answer": "Rapidash"},
    {"question": "Which is the legendary dog fire Pokemon of Johto?", "answer": "Entei"},
    {"question": "Weezing belongs to who?", "answer": "James"},
    {"question": "What is Gastly's secondary type except ghost?", "answer": "Poison"},
    {"question": "What is the last move Charizard used to defeat Pidgeot?", "answer": "Seismic toss"},
    {"question": "In the episode 'Gymbaliar', what Pokemon does Brock catch?", "answer": "Croagunk"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does James get in the episode 'Two Degrees of Separation'?", "answer": "Carnivine"},
    {"question": "In 'Gettin' Twiggy With it', what Pokemon does Ash catch?", "answer": "Turtwig"},
    {"question": "What is the name of the new girl Ash and Brock meet in the Sinnoh Region?", "answer": "Dawn"},
    {"question": "What type is Lucario?", "answer": "Fighting and Steel"},
    {"question": "I want to be the best Pokemon master ever. Who am I?", "answer": "Ash"},
    {"question": "I was Ash's very first Pokemon. Who am I?", "answer": "Pikachu"},
    {"question": "I am Ash's female traveling companion from the Sinnoh region. I want to be a top Pokemon coordinator. Who am I?", "answer": "Dawn"},
    {"question": "I am Ash's male traveling companion. I am the former gym leader from Pewter City. Who am I?", "answer": "Brock"},
    {"question": "I am Ash's rival from the Sinnoh region. I only care about strong Pokemon and release any Pokemon that is weak or does not reach my standards. Who am I?", "answer": "Paul"},
    {"question": "I am the female member of Team Rocket. I have pinkish-red hair and blue eyes. I am self centered and care about my hair and makeup. Who am I?", "answer": "Jessie"},
    {"question": "I am the male member of Team Rocket. I have purple hair and green eyes. I am evil a lot of the time, but sometimes I show a caring side. Who am I?", "answer": "James"},
    {"question": "I am a Pokemon and a member of Team Rocket. I am one of only a few Pokemon that can talk. Who am I?", "answer": "Meowth"},
    {"question": "I am a fire type Pokemon that resembles a monkey. I was released by Paul because he thought I was weak. After this event, Ash offered for me to join his team. Who am I?", "answer": "Chimchar"},
    {"question": "What are Bagon's two weaknesses?", "answer": "Dragon and Ice"},
    {"question": "When fighting a Xatu, a Spark attack will do more damage than Fire Blast.", "answer": "True"},
    {"question": "Which move will do the most damage to an Altaria?", "answer": "Blizzard"},
    {"question": "How many members are there of the Squirtle Squad?", "answer": "5"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon, in the episode 'Bulbasaur and the Hidden Village', did Misty want to catch?", "answer": "Oddish"},
    {"question": "What was the name of Charmander's original trainer?", "answer": "Damien"},
    {"question": "Who kicked Mankey?", "answer": "James"},
    {"question": "Where is the Tower of Terror located?", "answer": "Lavender Town"},
    {"question": "In the episode 'Bulbasaur and the Hidden Village', what is Bulbasaur's special attack?", "answer": "Vine Whip"},
    {"question": "Which city did Ash reach after capturing Primeape?", "answer": "Celadon City"},
    {"question": "Ash's hat is an official Pokemon League hat.", "answer": "true"},
    {"question": "How many Pokemon lived in the Tower of Terror?", "answer": "3"},
    {"question": "What is May's brother's name?", "answer": "Max"},
    {"question": "Does May's brother have any Pokemon?", "answer": "No"},
    {"question": "What was May's first Pokemon?", "answer": "Torchic"},
    {"question": "What was Brock before he joined Ash on his journey?", "answer": "A gym leader"},
    {"question": "What type of Pokemon does Misty have?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "Does May have a Bulbasaur?", "answer": "yes"},
    {"question": "What is the name of the nurse in all the Pokemon centers?", "answer": "Joy"},
    {"question": "One episode taken out of U.S. rotation because of the events of 9-11.", "answer": "true"},
    {"question": "The episode, 'Electric Soldier Porygon,' give 700 Japanese children seizures.", "answer": "true"},
    {"question": "Another episode, 'Holiday at Acapulco,' caused problems because of ...", "answer": "A cross-dressing man"},
    {"question": "How many episodes were delayed because they were 'too Japanese'?", "answer": "2"},
    {"question": "In the episode 'Princess vs. Princess,' which Pokemon did Misty win the competition with?", "answer": "Psyduck"},
    {"question": "In 'The Purr-fect Hero,' what Japanese holiday was being celebrated?", "answer": "Kids' Day"},
    {"question": "Most of the problem episodes appeared during which season?", "answer": "First"},
    {"question": "What year were the Christmas specials aired in the U.S.?", "answer": "1999"},
    {"question": "'Slowking's Day' appears in what season?", "answer": "3"},
    {"question": "Brock has how many brothers and sisters?", "answer": "9"},
    {"question": "How many years had the Maiden of Maiden's Peak waited for her true love to return to her?", "answer": "2,000 years"},
    {"question": "What is the name of the trainer who was waiting for Ash in the Viridian Forest?", "answer": "Samurai"},
    {"question": "Who gave Ash his first Pokemon?", "answer": "Professor Oak"},
    {"question": "In which city did Ash's first gym battle take place?", "answer": "Pewter City"},
    {"question": "What is the name of the famous stone that was believed to come from outer space?", "answer": "Moon Stone"},
    {"question": "What is Brock's father's name?", "answer": "Flint"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does James buy aboard the St. Anne?", "answer": "Magikarp"},
    {"question": "James comes from a rich family.", "answer": "True"},
    {"question": "What is the only move Ditto can learn?", "answer": "Transform"},
    {"question": "Which Pokemon steals other pokemon for his trainer?", "answer": "Farfetch'd"},
    {"question": "What attack does Gyarados use to get Ash, Misty, Brock, Pikachu, and Team Rocket away?", "answer": "Dragon Rage"},
    {"question": "Whose bike does Ash break?", "answer": "Misty"},
    {"question": "Which Pokemon's song puts everyone to sleep?", "answer": "Jigglypuff"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon hatched from Ash's egg?", "answer": "Phanpy"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon did Misty catch in the Whirl Islands?", "answer": "Corsola"},
    {"question": "What two Pokemon save Ash's egg from being stolen by Team Rocket?", "answer": "Togepi and Kangaskhan"},
    {"question": "What color was Ash's egg?", "answer": "blue"},
    {"question": "What did Sakura's Eevee evolve into?", "answer": "Espeon"},
    {"question": "Did Ash leave Bulbasaur with Prof. Oak in 'Bulbasaur... The Ambassador'?", "answer": "yes"},
    {"question": "Who pretended he was Prof. Oak in 'Will The Real Oak Please Stand Up'?", "answer": "James"},
    {"question": "What was the name of the baby Lugia?", "answer": "Silver"},
    {"question": "What is the name of the guy who wanted to catch Suicune?", "answer": "Eusine"},
    {"question": "What is the name of Richie's Pikachu?", "answer": "Sparky"},
    {"question": "Is Professor Oak Gary's grandpa?", "answer": "True"},
    {"question": "Lugia is intended to be the guardian of what?", "answer": "Legendary Bird Pokemon"},
    {"question": "Which Pokémon was gifted to Misty by Tracey?", "answer": "Azurill"},
    {"question": "There are how many variations of Unown?", "answer": "28"},
    {"question": "Who created Mewtwo?", "answer": "Giovanni"},
    {"question": "What was the first Pokemon to appear in the animated series?", "answer": "Gengar"},
    {"question": "Which Pokemon's Pokedex reference number is the same as the first three digits of its weight in pounds?", "answer": "Scyther"},
    {"question": "Gyarados was modeled after what legendary sea monster?", "answer": "Kraken"},
    {"question": "Out of the 26 letters in the English alphabet, the most Pokemon begin with which letter?", "answer": "S"},
    {"question": "If it was an actual species, Furret would logically belong to which family of mammals?", "answer": "Mustelidae"},
    {"question": "What was the first word Meowth (of Team Rocket) learned?", "answer": "Rocket"},
    {"question": "What species of flower was Vileplume modeled after?", "answer": "Rafflesia"},
    {"question": "According to Misty, she hates three things. Carrots and bugs are two. Which is the third?", "answer": "peppers"},
    {"question": "Which Pokemon character is named after a legendary Germanic sea siren whose beautiful song lured sailors to their deaths?", "answer": "Lorelei"},
    {"question": "What is the only Pokemon species recognized as having its own distinct verbal language?", "answer": "Jynx"},
    {"question": "Which Pokemon appeared on a wristwatch in one episode of 'The Powerpuff Girls'?", "answer": "Jigglypuff"},
    {"question": "Which Pokemon originally had a six-pointed star on its forehead?", "answer": "Alakazam"},
    {"question": "How many siblings does Brock have?", "answer": "9"},
    {"question": "Kabutops gets its name from...", "answer": "A Japanese war helmet"},
    {"question": "Umbreon gets its name from the Latin word umbra, which means...", "answer": "Shadow"},
    {"question": "Prof. Oak was inspired to become a Pokemon researcher after seeing a fossil of what Pokemon?", "answer": "Omanyte"},
    {"question": "If you lived in Azalea Town, you would most likely love which Pokemon?", "answer": "Slowpoke"},
    {"question": "If you wanted to capture a Snorlax, what Apricorn would you give Kurt to maximize your chances of capturing it?", "answer": "Black Apricorn"},
    {"question": "What city has a 'Mysterious Blue Aura' surrounding it?", "answer": "Cerulean City"},
    {"question": "What is the shortest Pokemon?", "answer": "Diglett"},
    {"question": "Where did Prof. Oak teach before coming to Pallet to start off new trainers?", "answer": "Celadon University"},
    {"question": "Misty's original home is the Cerulean City.", "answer": "true"},
    {"question": "What color was Misty's bike?", "answer": "Orange"},
    {"question": "What color did the Squirtle Squad want to change Misty's hair color to?", "answer": "Purple"},
    {"question": "When Ash goes to get his first Pokemon, who does he originally choose first?", "answer": "Squirtle"},
    {"question": "What was the first Pokemon Ash tried to capture?", "answer": "Pidgey"},
    {"question": "What color is Misty's hairbow?", "answer": "Blue"},
    {"question": "What color are Ash's eyes?", "answer": "Brown"},
    {"question": "What level do Chinchou evolve into Lanturn?", "answer": "Level 27"},
    {"question": "At what level does Squirtle learn Hydro Pump in Pokemon Red/Blue/Yellow?", "answer": "Level 42"},
    {"question": "Can you catch Oddish in 'Pokemon Blue' Game?", "answer": "No"},
    {"question": "What is the name of Ash's father in TV episodes?", "answer": "unknown"},
    {"question": "What is the name of the Pokemon that Brock catches first?", "answer": "Zubat"},
    {"question": "Who beats Ash in the Pokemon League?", "answer": "Ritchie"},
    {"question": "Where does Ash catch a Heracross?", "answer": "Johto"},
    {"question": "What kinds of Pokemon does the Gym Leader of Violet City use?", "answer": "Flying and Normal"},
    {"question": "Name the Pokemon. A Pokemon who sleeps and grows after eating a mountain.", "answer": "Larvitar"},
    {"question": "What is Entei known as?", "answer": "Legendary Dog"},
    {"question": "What is Ash's name in Japanese?", "answer": "Satoshi"},
    {"question": "What is the name of the Game Boy Advance Pokemon game released on 17 March 2003?", "answer": "Ruby"},
    {"question": "Which Pokemon does Tyrogue evolve into if Attack is less than Defense?", "answer": "Hitmonchan"},
    {"question": "What type of Pokemon is Naoshi's Pokemon Subomi?", "answer": "Grass"},
    {"question": "What is the name of James' Pokemon in place of his Victreebel?", "answer": "Masukippa"},
    {"question": "What causes Jigglypuff to sing?", "answer": "Looking into its eyes"},
    {"question": "In Pokemon Blue, what is the first move Jigglypuff learns?", "answer": "Sing"},
    {"question": "Approximately how much does Jigglypuff weigh?", "answer": "12 lbs"},
    {"question": "What can Jigglypuff do to make itself sing longer?", "answer": "Inflate"},
    {"question": "What number is Jigglypuff?", "answer": "39"},
    {"question": "Who's the Boss of Team Rocket?", "answer": "Giovanni"},
    {"question": "Who's Giovanni's mother?", "answer": "Madam Boss"},
    {"question": "What's James' Japanese name?", "answer": "Kojiro"},
    {"question": "What is Jessie's Mother's name?", "answer": "Miyamato"},
    {"question": "In a 'Pokemon Chronicles' episode, where is it shown that Jessie and James first meet?", "answer": "Team Rocket"},
    {"question": "What is Giovanni's Japanese name?", "answer": "Sakaki"},
    {"question": "Which Pokemon can learn all the moves?", "answer": "Mew"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Ash have 30x of?", "answer": "Tauros"},
    {"question": "Which Legendary Pokemon did Ash's Charizard beat?", "answer": "Articuno"},
    {"question": "Which Pokemon is on the Cover of Pokemon Blue?", "answer": "Blastoise"},
    {"question": "Which Pokemon is on the Cover of Pokemon Red?", "answer": "Charizard"},
    {"question": "Which Pokemon is on the Cover of Pokemon Yellow?", "answer": "Pikachu"},
    {"question": "Which Pokemon is on the Cover of Pokemon Green?", "answer": "Venasaur"},
    {"question": "Which Pokemon is on the Cover of Pokemon Silver?", "answer": "Lugia"},
    {"question": "Which Pokemon is on the Cover of Pokemon Gold?", "answer": "Ho-oh"},
    {"question": "Which Pokemon is on the Cover of Pokemon Crystal?", "answer": "Suicine"},
    {"question": "Which Pokemon is on the Cover of Pokemon Ruby?", "answer": "Groudon"},
    {"question": "Which Pokemon is on the Cover of Pokemon Sapphire?", "answer": "Kyogre"},
    {"question": "Which Pokemon is on the Cover of Pokemon Emerald?", "answer": "Rayquaza"},
    {"question": "Which Pokemon is on the Cover of Pokemon Diamond?", "answer": "Dialga"},
    {"question": "Which Pokemon is on the Cover of Pokemon Pearl?", "answer": "Palkia"},
    {"question": "Which Pokemon is on the Cover of Pokemon Platinum?", "answer": "Giratina"},
    {"question": "Which Pokemon is on the Cover of Pokemon Black?", "answer": "Reshiram"},
    {"question": "Which Pokemon is on the Cover of Pokemon White?", "answer": "Zekrom"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon is exclusive in the game Pokemon XD: Gale of Darkness?", "answer": "Shadow Lugia"},
    {"question": "Who is the fire starter in Pokemon Red/Blue?", "answer": "Charmander"},
    {"question": "Who is the water starter in Pokemon Red/Blue?", "answer": "Squirtle"},
    {"question": "Who is the grass starter in Pokemon Red/Blue?", "answer": "Bulbasaur"},
    {"question": "Who is the starter in Pokemon Yellow?", "answer": "Pikachu"},
    {"question": "Who is the fire starter in Pokemon Gold/Silver/Crystal?", "answer": "Cyndaquil"},
    {"question": "Who is the water starter in Pokemon Gold/Silver/Crystal?", "answer": "Totodile"},
    {"question": "Who is the grass starter in Pokemon Gold/Silver/Crystal?", "answer": "Chikorita"},
    {"question": "Who is the fire starter in Pokemon Ruby/Emerald/Sapphire?", "answer": " Torchic"},
    {"question": "Who is the water starter in Pokemon Ruby/Emerald/Sapphire?", "answer": "Mudkip"},
    {"question": "Who is the grass starter in Pokemon Ruby/Emerald/Sapphire?", "answer": "Treecko"},
    {"question": "Who is the fire starter in Pokemon Diamond/Pearl?", "answer": "Chimchar"},
    {"question": "Who is the water starter in Pokemon Diamond/Pearl?", "answer": "Piplup"},
    {"question": "Who is the grass starter in Pokemon Diamond/Pearl?", "answer": "Turtwig"},
    {"question": "Who is the fire starter in Pokemon White/Black?", "answer": "Pokabu"},
    {"question": "Who is the water starter in Pokemon White/Black?", "answer": "Mijumaru"},
    {"question": "Who is the grass starter in Pokemon White/Black?", "answer": "Tsutarja"},
    {"question": "Who is the starter Pokemon in Pokemon Rumble?", "answer": "Rattata"},
    {"question": "Who is the starter Pokemon in Pokemon XD: Gale of Darkness?", "answer": "Eevee"},
    {"question": "Which Pokeball catches Pokemon without fail?", "answer": "Master Ball"},
    {"question": "Which Pokeball allows you to catch Pokemon in the Safari Zone?", "answer": "Safari Ball"},
    {"question": "Which Pokeball works better on Pokémon hooked by a rod?", "answer": "Lure Ball"},
    {"question": "Which Pokeball works better on Pokémon of levels lower than the Pokémon currently in battle?", "answer": "Level Ball"},
    {"question": "Which Pokeball works better on Pokémon that evolve when exposed to radiation from a Moon Stone?", "answer": "Moon Ball"},
    {"question": "Which Pokeball makes a Pokémon more friendly when caught?", "answer": "Friend Ball"},
    {"question": "Which Pokeball works better on Pokémon of the opposite gender?", "answer": "Love Ball"},
    {"question": "Which Pokeball works better on heavier Pokémon?", "answer": "Heavy Ball"},
    {"question": "Which Pokeball works better on fast Pokémon (Generation IV) or Pokémon likely to flee from battle (Generation II)?", "answer": "Fast Ball"},
    {"question": "Which Pokeball allows the player to catch wild Pokémon in the Bug-Catching Contest?", "answer": "Sport Ball"},
    {"question": "Which Pokeball was made in commemoration of some event?", "answer": "Premier Ball"},
    {"question": "Which Pokeball works better on Pokémon whose species have already been caught?", "answer": "Repeat Ball"},
    {"question": "Which Pokeball works better in battles that have lasted longer?", "answer": "Timer Ball"},
    {"question": "Which Pokeball works better on lower-level Pokémon?", "answer": "Nest Ball"},
    {"question": "Which Pokeball works better on Water- and Bug-type Pokémon?", "answer": "Net Ball"},
    {"question": "Which Pokeball works better on Pokémon encountered underwater/while Surfing and fishing?", "answer": "Dive Ball"},
    {"question": "Which Pokeball makes a Pokémon more friendly when caught?", "answer": "Luxury Ball"},
    {"question": "Which Pokeball fully restores a caught Pokémon's HP, PP, and status?", "answer": "Heal Ball"},
    {"question": "Which Pokeball works better when used early in the battle?", "answer": "Quick Ball"},
    {"question": "Which Pokeball works better when used in caves or at night?", "answer": "Dusk Ball"},
    {"question": "Which Pokeball contains an event Pokemon?", "answer": "Cherish Ball"},
    {"question": "Which Pokeball Recatches Pokémon sent through Pal Park?", "answer": "Park Ball"},
    {"question": "What badge do you receive from Pewter City?", "answer": "Boulder Badge"},
    {"question": "What badge do you receive from Cerulean City?", "answer": "Cascade Badge"},
    {"question": "What badge do you receive from Vermilion City?", "answer": "Thunder Badge"},
    {"question": "What badge do you receive from Celadon City?", "answer": "Rainbow Badge"},
    {"question": "What badge do you receive from Fuchsia City?", "answer": "Soul Badge"},
    {"question": "What badge do you receive from Saffron City?", "answer": "Marsh Badge"},
    {"question": "What badge do you receive from Cinnabar Island?", "answer": "Volcano Badge"},
    {"question": "What badge do you receive from Virigian City?", "answer": "Earth Badge"},
    {"question": "What badge do you receive from Mikan Island?", "answer": "Coral-Eye Badge"},
    {"question": "What badge do you receive from Navel Island?", "answer": "Sea Ruby Badge"},
    {"question": "What badge do you receive from Trovita Island?", "answer": "Spike Shell Badge"},
    {"question": "What badge do you receive from Kumquat Island?", "answer": "Jade Star Badge"},
    {"question": "What badge do you receive from Violet City?", "answer": "Zephyr Bade"},
    {"question": "What badge do you receive from Azalea Town?", "answer": "Hive Badge"},
    {"question": "What badge do you receive from Goldenrod City?", "answer": "Plain Badge"},
    {"question": "What badge do you receive from Ecruteak City?", "answer": "Fog Badge"},
    {"question": "What badge do you receive from Cianwood City?", "answer": "Storm Badge"},
    {"question": "What badge do you receive from Olivine City?", "answer": "Mineral Badge"},
    {"question": "What badge do you receive from Mahogany Town?", "answer": "Glacier Badge"},
    {"question": "What badge do you receive from Blackthorn City?", "answer": "Rising Badge"},
    {"question": "What badge do you receive from Rustboro City?", "answer": "Stone Badge"},
    {"question": "What badge do you receive from Dewford Town?", "answer": "Knuckle Badge"},
    {"question": "What badge do you receive from Mauville City?", "answer": "Dynamo Badge"},
    {"question": "What badge do you receive from Lavaridge Town?", "answer": "Heat Badge"},
    {"question": "What badge do you receive from Petalburg City?", "answer": "Balance Badge"},
    {"question": "What badge do you receive from Fortree City?", "answer": "Feather badge"},
    {"question": "What badge do you receive from Mossdeep City?", "answer": "Mind Bade"},
    {"question": "What badge do you receive from Sootopolis City?", "answer": "Rain Badge"},
    {"question": "What badge do you receive from Oreburgh City?", "answer": "Coal Badge"},
    {"question": "What badge do you receive from Eterna City?", "answer": "Forest Badge"},
    {"question": "What badge do you receive from Veilstone City?", "answer": "Cobble Badge"},
    {"question": "What badge do you receive from Pastoria City?", "answer": "Fen Badge"},
    {"question": "What badge do you receive from Heartorne City?", "answer": "Relic Badge"},
    {"question": "What badge do you receive from Canalave City?", "answer": "Mine Badge"},
    {"question": "What badge do you receive from Snowpoint City?", "answer": "Icicle Badge"},
    {"question": "What badge do you receive from Sunyshore City?", "answer": "Beacon Badge"},
    {"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Pewter City?", "answer": "Brock"},
    {"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Cerulean City?", "answer": "Misty"},
    {"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Vermilion City?", "answer": "Lt. Surge"},
    {"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Celadon City?", "answer": "Erika"},
    {"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Fushsia City?", "answer": "Koga"},
    {"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Saffron City?", "answer": "Sabrina"},
    {"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Cinnabar Island?", "answer": "Blaine"},
    {"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Viridian City?", "answer": "Giovanni"},
    {"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Mikan Island?", "answer": "Cissy"},
    {"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Navel Island?", "answer": "Danny"},
    {"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Trovita Island?", "answer": "Rudy"},
    {"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Kumquat Island?", "answer": "Luana"},
    {"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Violet City?", "answer": "Falkner"},
    {"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Azalea Town?", "answer": "Bugsy"},
    {"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Goldenrod City?", "answer": "Whitney"},
    {"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Ecruteak City?", "answer": "Morty"},
    {"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Cianwood City?", "answer": "Chuck"},
    {"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Olivine City?", "answer": "Jasmine"},
    {"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Mahogany Town?", "answer": "Pryce"},
    {"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Blackthorn City?", "answer": "Clair"},
    {"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Rustboro City?", "answer": "Roxanne"},
    {"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Dewford Town?", "answer": "Brawly"},
    {"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Mauville City?", "answer": "Wattson"},
    {"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Lavaridge Town?", "answer": "Flannery"},
    {"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Petarlburg City?", "answer": "Norman"},
    {"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Fortee City?", "answer": "Winona"},
    {"question": "Who are the Gym Leaders of Mossdeep City?", "answer": "Tate and Liza"},
    {"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Sootopolis City?", "answer": "Wallace"},
    {"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Oreburgh City?", "answer": "Roark"},
    {"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Eterna City?", "answer": "Gardenia"},
    {"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Veilstone City?", "answer": "Maylene"},
    {"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Pastoria City?", "answer": "Crasher Wake"},
    {"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Hearthorne City?", "answer": "Fantina"},
    {"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Canalave City?", "answer": "Byron"},
    {"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Snowpoint City?", "answer": "Candice"},
    {"question": "Who is the Gym Leader of Sunyshore City?", "answer": "Volkner"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Bulbasaur evolve into?", "answer": "Ivysaur"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Charmander evolve into?", "answer": "Charmeleon"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Squirtle evolve into?", "answer": "Wartortle"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Caterpie evolve into?", "answer": "Metapod"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Weedle evolve into?", "answer": "Kakuna"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Pidgey evolve into?", "answer": "Pidgeotto"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Rattata evolve into?", "answer": "Raticate"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Spearow evolve into?", "answer": "Fearow"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Ekans evolve into?", "answer": "Arbok"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Pichu evolve into?", "answer": "Pikachu"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Sandshrew evolve into?", "answer": "Sandslash"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Nidoran(male) evolve into?", "answer": "Nidorino"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Nidoran(female) evolve into?", "answer": "Nidorina"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Cleffa evolve into?", "answer": "Clefairy"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Vulpix evolve into?", "answer": "Ninetales"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Igglybuff evolve into?", "answer": "Jigglypuff"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Zubat evolve into?", "answer": "Golbat"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Oddish evolve into?", "answer": "Gloom"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Paras evolve into?", "answer": "Parasect"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Venonat evolve into?", "answer": "Venomoth"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Diglett evolve into?", "answer": "Dugtrio"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Meowth evolve into?", "answer": "Persian"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Psyduck evolve into?", "answer": "Golduck"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Mankey evolve into?", "answer": "Primeape"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Growlithe evolve into?", "answer": "Arcanine"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Poliwag evolve into?", "answer": "Poliwhirl"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Abra evolve into?", "answer": "Kadabra"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Machop evolve into?", "answer": "Machoke"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Bellsprout evolve into?", "answer": "Weepinbell"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Tentacool evolve into?", "answer": "Tentacruel"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Geodude evolve into?", "answer": "Graveler"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Ponyta evolve into?", "answer": "Rapidash"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Slowpoke evolve into at level 37?", "answer": "Slowbro"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Slowpoke evolve into when traded holding a King's Rock?", "answer": "Slowking"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Magnemite evolve into?", "answer": "Magneton"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Doduo evolve into?", "answer": "Dodrio"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Seel evolve into?", "answer": "Dewgong"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Grimer evolve into?", "answer": "Muk"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Shellder evolve into?", "answer": "Cloyster"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Gastly evolve into?", "answer": "Haunter"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Onix evolve into?", "answer": "Steelix"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Drowzee evolve into?", "answer": "Hypno"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Krabby evolve into?", "answer": "Kingler"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Voltorb evolve into?", "answer": "Electrode"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Exeggcute evolve into?", "answer": "Exeggutor"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Cubone evolve into?", "answer": "Marowak"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Tyrogue evolve into at level 20 if his attack > defense?", "answer": "Hitmonlee"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Tyrogue evolve into at level 20 if his attack < defense?", "answer": "Hitmonchan"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Tyrogue evolve into at level 20 if his attack = defense?", "answer": "Hitmontop"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Lickitung evolve into?", "answer": "Lickilicky"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Koffing evolve into?", "answer": "Weezing"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Rhyhorn evolve into?", "answer": "Rhydon"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Happiny evolve into?", "answer": "Chansey"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Tangela evolve into?", "answer": "Tangrowth"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Horsea evolve into?", "answer": "Seadra"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Goldeen evolve into?", "answer": "Seaking"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Staryu evolve into?", "answer": "Starmie"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Mime Jr. evolve into?", "answer": "Mr. Mime"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Scyther evolve into?", "answer": "Scizor"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Smoochum evolve into?", "answer": "Jynx"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Elekid evolve into?", "answer": "Electabuzz"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Magby evolve into?", "answer": "Magmar"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Magikarp evolve into?", "answer": "Gyarados"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Eevee evolve into when exposed to a Water Stone?", "answer": "Vaporeon"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Eevee evolve into when exposed to a Thunderstone?", "answer": "Jolteon"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Eevee evolve into when exposed to a Fire Stone?", "answer": "Flareon"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Eevee evolve into when happy durning the daytime?", "answer": "Espeon"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Eevee evolve into when happy durning the nighttime?", "answer": "Umbreon"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Eevee evolve into when leveled up in Eterna Forest?", "answer": "Leafeon"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Eevee evolve into when leveled up on Route 217?", "answer": "Glaceon"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Porygon evolve into?", "answer": "Porygon2"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Omanyte evolve into?", "answer": "Omastar"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Kabuto evolve into?", "answer": "Kabutops"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Munchlax evolve into?", "answer": "Snorlax"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Dratini evolve into?", "answer": "Dragonair"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Chikorita evolve into?", "answer": "Bayleef"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Cyndaquil evolve into?", "answer": "Quilava"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Totodile evolve into?", "answer": "Croconaw"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Sentret evolve into?", "answer": "Furret"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Hoothoot evolve into?", "answer": "Noctowl"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Ledyba evolve into?", "answer": "Ledian"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Spinarak evolve into?", "answer": "Ariados"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Chinchou evolve into?", "answer": "Lanturn"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Togepi evolve into?", "answer": "Togetic"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Natu evolve into?", "answer": "Xatu"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Mareep evolve into?", "answer": "Flaaffy"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Azurill evolve into?", "answer": "Marill"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Bonsly evolve into?", "answer": "Sudowoodo"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Hoppip evolve into?", "answer": "Skiploom"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Aipom evolve into?", "answer": "Ambipom"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Sunkern evolve into?", "answer": "Sunflora"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Yanma evolve into?", "answer": "Yanmega"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Wooper evolve into?", "answer": "Quagsire"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Murkrow evolve into?", "answer": "Honchkrow"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Misdreavus evolve into?", "answer": "Mismagius"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Wynaut evolve into?", "answer": "Wobbuffet"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Pineco evolve into?", "answer": "Forretress"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Gligar evolve into?", "answer": "Gliscor"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Snubbull evolve into?", "answer": "Granbull"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Sneasel evolve into?", "answer": "Weavile"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Teddiursa evolve into?", "answer": "Ursaring"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Slugma evolve into?", "answer": "Magcargo"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Swinub evolve into?", "answer": "Piloswine"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Remoraid evolve into?", "answer": "Octillery"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Mantyke evolve into?", "answer": "Mantine"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Houndour evolve into?", "answer": "Houndoom"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Phanpy evolve into?", "answer": "Donphan"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Larvitar evolve into?", "answer": "Pupitar"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Treecko evolve into?", "answer": "Grovyle"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Torchic evolve into?", "answer": "Combusken"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Mudkip evolve into?", "answer": "Marshtomp"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Poochyena evolve into?", "answer": "Mightyena"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Zigzagoon evolve into?", "answer": "Linoone"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Wurmple evolve into that could evolve into a Beautifly?", "answer": "Silcoon"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Wurmple evolve into that could evolve into a Dustox?", "answer": "Cascoon"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Lotad evolve into?", "answer": "Lombre"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Seedot evolve into?", "answer": "Nuzleaf"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Taillow evolve into?", "answer": "Swellow"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Wingull evolve into?", "answer": "Pelipper"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Ralts evolve into?", "answer": "Kirlia"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Surskit evolve into?", "answer": "Masquerain"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Shroomish evolve into?", "answer": "Breloom"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Slakoth evolve into?", "answer": "Vigoroth"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Nincada evolve into at level 20?", "answer": "Ninjask"},
    {"question": "If Nincada evolves and you have a spare spot in your party and an extra Poke Ball what Pokemon appears in your party?", "answer": "Shedinja"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Whismur evolve into?", "answer": "Loudred"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Makuhita evolve into?", "answer": "Hariyama"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Nosepass evolve into?", "answer": "Probopass"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Skitty evolve into?", "answer": "Delcatty"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Aron evolve into?", "answer": "Lairon"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Meditite evolve into?", "answer": "Medicham"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Electrike evolve into?", "answer": "Manectric"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Budew evolve into?", "answer": "Roselia"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Gulpin evolve into?", "answer": "Swalot"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Carvanha evolve into?", "answer": "Sharpedo"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Wailmer evolve into?", "answer": "Wailord"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Numel evolve into?", "answer": "Camerupt"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Spoink evolve into?", "answer": "Grumpig"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Trapinch evolve into?", "answer": "Vibrava"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Cacnea evolve into?", "answer": "Cacturne"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Swablu evolve into?", "answer": "Altaria"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Barboach evolve into?", "answer": "Whiscash"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Corphish evolve into?", "answer": "Crawdaunt"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Baltoy evolve into?", "answer": "Claydol"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Lileep evolve into?", "answer": "Cradily"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Anorith evolve into?", "answer": "Armaldo"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Feebas evolve into?", "answer": "Milotic"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Shuppet evolve into?", "answer": "Banette"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Duskull evolve into?", "answer": "Dusclops"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Chingling evolve into?", "answer": "Chimecho"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Snorunt evolve into at level 42?", "answer": "Glalie"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Snorunt evolve into if female and exposed to radiation from a Dawn Stone?", "answer": "Froslass"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Spheal evolve into?", "answer": "Sealeo"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Clamperl evolve into when traded holding a DeepSeaTooth?", "answer": "Huntail"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Clamperl evolve into when traded holding a DeepSeaScale?", "answer": "Gorebyss"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Bagon evolve into?", "answer": "Shelgon"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Beldum evolve into?", "answer": "Metang"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Turtwig evolve into?", "answer": "Grotle"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Chimchar evolve into?", "answer": "Monferno"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Piplup evolve into?", "answer": "Prinplup"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Starly evolve into?", "answer": "Staravia"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Bidoof evolve into?", "answer": "Bibarel"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Kricketot evolve into?", "answer": "Kricketune"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Shinx evolve into?", "answer": "Luxio"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Cranidos evolve into?", "answer": "Rampardos"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Shieldon evolve into?", "answer": "Bastiodon"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does a male Burmy evolve into at level 20?", "answer": "Mothim"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does a female Burmy evolve into at level 20?", "answer": "Wormadam"},
    {"question": "What cloak will a Wormadam have if the location where it last battled, right before it evolved was outside or in tall grass?", "answer": "Plant Cloak"},
    {"question": "What cloak will a Wormadam have if the location where it last battled, right before it evolved was in a cave, on a beach, or faced a Pokémon from a Honey tree?", "answer": "Sandy Cloak"},
    {"question": "What cloak will a Wormadam have if the location where it last battled, right before it evolved was outside or in a building?", "answer": "Trash Cloak"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Combee evolve into?", "answer": "Vespiquen"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Buizel evolve into?", "answer": "Floatzel"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Cherubi evolve into?", "answer": "Cherrim"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Shellos evolve into?", "answer": "Gastrodon"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Drifloon evolve into?", "answer": "Drifblim"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Buneary evolve into?", "answer": "Lopunny"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Glameow evolve into?", "answer": "Purugly"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Stunky evolve into?", "answer": "Skuntank"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Bronzor evolve into?", "answer": "Bronzong"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Gible evolve into?", "answer": "Gabite"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Riolu evolve into?", "answer": "Lucario"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Hippopotas evolve into?", "answer": "Hippowdon"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Skorupi evolve into?", "answer": "Drapion"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Croagunk evolve into?", "answer": "Toxicroak"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Finneon evolve into?", "answer": "Lumineon"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Snover evolve into?", "answer": "Abomasnow"},
    {"question": "If Rotom isnt possesing an appliance what form would he be?", "answer": "Normal Rotom"},
    {"question": "If Rotom possessed a Toaster Oven what form would he change to?", "answer": "Heat Rotom"},
    {"question": "If Rotom possessed a Washing Machine what form would he change to?", "answer": "Wash Rotom"},
    {"question": "If Rotom possessed a Refrigerator what form would he change to?", "answer": "Frost Rotom"},
    {"question": "If Rotom possessed a Fan what form would he change to?", "answer": "Fan Rotom"},
    {"question": "If Rotom possessed a Lawnmower what form would he change to?", "answer": "Mow Rotom"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Giratina change into if in Distortion World or holding a Griseous Orb?", "answer": "Origin Form"},
    {"question": "What form does Giratina change into if in the normal Pokemon World?", "answer": "Altered Form"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Ivysaur evolve into?", "answer": "Venusaur"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Charmeleon evolve into?", "answer": "Charizard"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Wartortle evolve into?", "answer": "Blastoise"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Metapod evolve into?", "answer": "Butterfree"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Kakuna evolve into?", "answer": "Beedrill"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Pidgeotto evolve into?", "answer": "Pidgeot"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Pikachu evolve into?", "answer": "Raichu"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Nidorina evolve into?", "answer": "Nidoqueen"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Nidorino evolve into?", "answer": "Nidoking"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Clefairy evolve into?", "answer": "Clefable"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Jigglypuff evolve into?", "answer": "Wigglytuff"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Golbat evolve into?", "answer": "Crobat"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Gloom evolve into when exposed to a Leaf Stone?", "answer": "Vileplume"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Gloom evolve into when exposed to a Sun Stone?", "answer": "Bellossom"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Poliwhirl evolve into when exposed to a Water Stone?", "answer": "Poliwrath"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Poliwhirl evolve into when traded holding a King's Rock?", "answer": "Politoed"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Kadabra evolve into?", "answer": "Alakazam"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Machoke evolve into?", "answer": "Machamp"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Weepinbell evolve into?", "answer": "Victreebel"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Graveler evolve into?", "answer": "Golem"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Magneton evolve into?", "answer": "Magnezone"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Haunter evolve into?", "answer": "Gengar"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Rhydon evolve into?", "answer": "Rhyperior"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Chansey evolve into?", "answer": "Blissey"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Seadra evolve into?", "answer": "Kingdra"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Electabuzz evolve into?", "answer": "Electivire"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Magmar evolve into?", "answer": "Magmortar"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Porygon2 evolve into?", "answer": "Porygon-Z"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Dragonair evolve into?", "answer": "Dragonite"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Bayleef evolve into?", "answer": "Meganium"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Quilava evolve into?", "answer": "Typhlosion"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Croconaw evolve into?", "answer": "Feraligatr"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Togetic evolve into?", "answer": "Togekiss"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Flaaffy evolve into?", "answer": "Ampharos"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Marill evolve into?", "answer": "Azumarill"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Skiploom evolve into?", "answer": "Jumpluff"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Piloswine evolve into?", "answer": "Mamoswine"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Pupitar evolve into?", "answer": "Tyranitar"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Grovyle evolve into?", "answer": "Sceptile"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Combusken evolve into?", "answer": "Blaziken"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Marshtomp evolve into?", "answer": "Swampert"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Silcoon evolve into?", "answer": "Beautifly"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Cascoon evolve into?", "answer": "Dustox"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Lombre evolve into?", "answer": "Ludicolo"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Nuzleaf evolve into?", "answer": "Shiftry"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Kirlia evolve into at level 30?", "answer": "Gardevoir"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Kirlia evolve into if male and exposed to radiation from a Dawn Stone?", "answer": "Gallade"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Vigoroth evolve into?", "answer": "Slaking"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Loudred evolve into?", "answer": "Exploud"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Lairon evolve into?", "answer": "Aggron"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Roselia evolve into?", "answer": "Roserade"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Vibrava evolve into?", "answer": "Flygon"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Dusclops evolve into?", "answer": "Dusknoir"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Sealeo evolve into?", "answer": "Walrein"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Shelgon evolve into?", "answer": "Salamence"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Metang evolve into?", "answer": "Metagross"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Grotle evolve into?", "answer": "Torterra"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Monferno evolve into?", "answer": "Infernape"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Prinplup evolve into?", "answer": "Empoleon"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Staravia evolve into?", "answer": "Staraptor"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Luxio evolve into?", "answer": "Luxray"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Gabite evolve into?", "answer": "Garchomp"},
    {"question": "What are Bulbasaur's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass  and  Poison"},
    {"question": "What are Ivysaur's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass  and  Poison"},
    {"question": "What are Venusaur's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Poison"},
    {"question": "What are Charmander's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire"},
    {"question": "What are Charmeleon's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire"},
    {"question": "What are Charizard's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Squirtle's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Wartortle's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Blastoise's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Caterpie's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug"},
    {"question": "What are Metapod's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug"},
    {"question": "What are Butterfree's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Weedle's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Poison"},
    {"question": "What are Kakuna's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Poison"},
    {"question": "What are Beedrill's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Poison"},
    {"question": "What are Pidgey's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Pidgeotto's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Pidgeot's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Rattata's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Raticate's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Spearow's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Fearow's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Ekans's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison"},
    {"question": "What are Arbok's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison"},
    {"question": "What are Pikachu's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric"},
    {"question": "What are Raichu's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric"},
    {"question": "What are Sandshrew's type(s)?", "answer": "Ground"},
    {"question": "What are Sandslash's type(s)?", "answer": "Ground"},
    {"question": "What are Nidoran[male]'s type(s)?", "answer": "Poison"},
    {"question": "What are Nidorina's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison"},
    {"question": "What are Nidoqueen's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison and Ground"},
    {"question": "What are Nidoran[female]'s type(s)?", "answer": "Poison"},
    {"question": "What are Nidorino's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison"},
    {"question": "What are Nidoking's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison and Ground"},
    {"question": "What are Clefairy's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Clefable's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Vulpix's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire"},
    {"question": "What are Ninetales's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire"},
    {"question": "What are Jigglypuff's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Wigglytuff's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Zubat's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Golbat's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Oddish's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Poison"},
    {"question": "What are Gloom's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Poison"},
    {"question": "What are Vileplume's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Poison"},
    {"question": "What are Paras's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Grass"},
    {"question": "What are Parasect's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Grass"},
    {"question": "What are Venonat's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Poison"},
    {"question": "What are Venomoth's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Poison"},
    {"question": "What are Diglett's type(s)?", "answer": "Ground"},
    {"question": "What are Dugtrio's type(s)?", "answer": "Ground"},
    {"question": "What are Meowth's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Persian's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Psyduck's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Golduck's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Mankey's type(s)?", "answer": "Fighting"},
    {"question": "What are Primeape's type(s)?", "answer": "Fighting"},
    {"question": "What are Growlithe's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire"},
    {"question": "What are Arcanine's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire"},
    {"question": "What are Poliwag's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Poliwhirl's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Poliwrath's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Fighting"},
    {"question": "What are Abra's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Kadabra's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Alakazam's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Machop's type(s)?", "answer": "Fighting"},
    {"question": "What are Machoke's type(s)?", "answer": "Fighting"},
    {"question": "What are Machamp's type(s)?", "answer": "Fighting"},
    {"question": "What are Bellsprout's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Poison"},
    {"question": "What are Weepinbell's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Poison"},
    {"question": "What are Victreebel's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Poison"},
    {"question": "What are Tentacool's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Poison"},
    {"question": "What are Tentacruel's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Poison"},
    {"question": "What are Geodude's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock and Ground"},
    {"question": "What are Graveler's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock and Ground"},
    {"question": "What are Golem's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock and Ground"},
    {"question": "What are Ponyta's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire"},
    {"question": "What are Rapidash's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire"},
    {"question": "What are Slowpoke's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Slowbro's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Magnemite's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric and Steel"},
    {"question": "What are Magneton's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric and Steel"},
    {"question": "What are Farfetch'd's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Doduo's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Dodrio's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Seel's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Dewgong's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Ice"},
    {"question": "What are Grimer's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison"},
    {"question": "What are Muk's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison"},
    {"question": "What are Shellder's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Cloyster's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Ice"},
    {"question": "What are Gastly's type(s)?", "answer": "Ghost and Poison"},
    {"question": "What are Haunter's type(s)?", "answer": "Ghost and Poison"},
    {"question": "What are Gengar's type(s)?", "answer": "Ghost and Poison"},
    {"question": "What are Onix's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock and Ground"},
    {"question": "What are Drowzee's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Hypno's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Krabby's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Kingler's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Voltorb's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric"},
    {"question": "What are Electrode's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric"},
    {"question": "What are Exeggcute's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Exeggutor's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Cubone's type(s)?", "answer": "Ground"},
    {"question": "What are Marowak's type(s)?", "answer": "Ground"},
    {"question": "What are Hitmonlee's type(s)?", "answer": "Fighting"},
    {"question": "What are Hitmonchan's type(s)?", "answer": "Fighting"},
    {"question": "What are Lickitung's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Koffing's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison"},
    {"question": "What are Weezing's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison"},
    {"question": "What are Rhyhorn's type(s)?", "answer": "Ground and Rock"},
    {"question": "What are Rhydon's type(s)?", "answer": "Ground and Rock"},
    {"question": "What are Chansey's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Tangela's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass"},
    {"question": "What are Kangaskhan's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Horsea's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Seadra's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Goldeen's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Seaking's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Staryu's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Starmie's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Mr. Mime's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Scyther's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Jynx's type(s)?", "answer": "Ice and Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Electabuzz's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric"},
    {"question": "What are Magmar's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire"},
    {"question": "What are Pinsir's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug"},
    {"question": "What are Tauros's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Magikarp's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Gyarados's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Lapras's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Ice"},
    {"question": "What are Ditto's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Eevee's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Vaporeon's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Jolteon's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric"},
    {"question": "What are Flareon's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire"},
    {"question": "What are Porygon's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Omanyte's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock and Water"},
    {"question": "What are Omastar's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock and Water"},
    {"question": "What are Kabuto's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock and Water"},
    {"question": "What are Kabutops's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock and Water"},
    {"question": "What are Aerodactyl's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Snorlax's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Articuno's type(s)?", "answer": "Ice and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Zapdos's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Moltres's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Dratini's type(s)?", "answer": "Dragon"},
    {"question": "What are Dragonair's type(s)?", "answer": "Dragon"},
    {"question": "What are Dragonite's type(s)?", "answer": "Dragon and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Mewtwo's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Mew's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Chikorita's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass"},
    {"question": "What are Bayleef's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass"},
    {"question": "What are Meganium's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass"},
    {"question": "What are Cyndaquil's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire"},
    {"question": "What are Quilava's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire"},
    {"question": "What are Typhlosion's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire"},
    {"question": "What are Totodile's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Croconaw's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Feraligatr's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Sentret's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Furret's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Hoothoot's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Noctowl's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Ledyba's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Ledian's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Spinarak's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Poison"},
    {"question": "What are Ariados's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Poison"},
    {"question": "What are Crobat's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Chinchou's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Electric"},
    {"question": "What are Lanturn's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Electric"},
    {"question": "What are Pichu's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric"},
    {"question": "What are Cleffa's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Igglybuff's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Togepi's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Togetic's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Natu's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Xatu's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Mareep's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric"},
    {"question": "What are Flaaffy's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric"},
    {"question": "What are Ampharos's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric"},
    {"question": "What are Bellossom's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass"},
    {"question": "What are Marill's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Azumarill's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Sudowoodo's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock"},
    {"question": "What are Politoed's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Hoppip's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Skiploom's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Jumpluff's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Aipom's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Sunkern's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass"},
    {"question": "What are Sunflora's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass"},
    {"question": "What are Yanma's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Wooper's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Ground"},
    {"question": "What are Quagsire's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Ground"},
    {"question": "What are Espeon's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Umbreon's type(s)?", "answer": "Dark"},
    {"question": "What are Murkrow's type(s)?", "answer": "Dark and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Slowking's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Misdreavus's type(s)?", "answer": "Ghost"},
    {"question": "What are Unown's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Wobbuffet's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Girafarig's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal and Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Pineco's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug"},
    {"question": "What are Forretress's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Steel"},
    {"question": "What are Dunsparce's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Gligar's type(s)?", "answer": "Ground and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Steelix's type(s)?", "answer": "Steel and Ground"},
    {"question": "What are Snubbull's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Granbull's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Qwilfish's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Poison"},
    {"question": "What are Scizor's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Steel"},
    {"question": "What are Shuckle's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Rock"},
    {"question": "What are Heracross's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Fighting"},
    {"question": "What are Sneasel's type(s)?", "answer": "Dark and Ice"},
    {"question": "What are Teddiursa's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Ursaring's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Slugma's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire"},
    {"question": "What are Magcargo's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire and Rock"},
    {"question": "What are Swinub's type(s)?", "answer": "Ice and Ground"},
    {"question": "What are Piloswine's type(s)?", "answer": "Ice and Ground"},
    {"question": "What are Corsola's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Rock"},
    {"question": "What are Remoraid's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Octillery's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Delibird's type(s)?", "answer": "Ice and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Mantine's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Skarmory's type(s)?", "answer": "Steel and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Houndour's type(s)?", "answer": "Dark and Fire"},
    {"question": "What are Houndoom's type(s)?", "answer": "Dark and Fire"},
    {"question": "What are Kingdra's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Dragon"},
    {"question": "What are Phanpy's type(s)?", "answer": "Ground"},
    {"question": "What are Donphan's type(s)?", "answer": "Ground"},
    {"question": "What are Porygon2's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Stantler's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Smeargle's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Tyrogue's type(s)?", "answer": "Fighting"},
    {"question": "What are Hitmontop's type(s)?", "answer": "Fighting"},
    {"question": "What are Smoochum's type(s)?", "answer": "Ice and Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Elekid's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric"},
    {"question": "What are Magby's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire"},
    {"question": "What are Miltank's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Blissey's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Raikou's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric"},
    {"question": "What are Entei's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire"},
    {"question": "What are Suicune's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Larvitar's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock and Ground"},
    {"question": "What are Pupitar's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock and Ground"},
    {"question": "What are Tyranitar's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock and Dark"},
    {"question": "What are Lugia's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Ho-Oh's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Celebi's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic and Grass"},
    {"question": "What are Treecko's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass"},
    {"question": "What are Grovyle's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass"},
    {"question": "What are Sceptile's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass"},
    {"question": "What are Torchic's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire"},
    {"question": "What are Combusken's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire and Fighting"},
    {"question": "What are Blaziken's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire and Fighting"},
    {"question": "What are Mudkip's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Marshtomp's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Ground"},
    {"question": "What are Swampert's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Ground"},
    {"question": "What are Poochyena's type(s)?", "answer": "Dark"},
    {"question": "What are Mightyena's type(s)?", "answer": "Dark"},
    {"question": "What are Zigzagoon's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Linoone's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Wurmple's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug"},
    {"question": "What are Silcoon's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug"},
    {"question": "What are Beautifly's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Cascoon's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug"},
    {"question": "What are Dustox's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Poison"},
    {"question": "What are Lotad's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Grass"},
    {"question": "What are Lombre's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Grass"},
    {"question": "What are Ludicolo's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Grass"},
    {"question": "What are Seedot's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass"},
    {"question": "What are Nuzleaf's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Dark"},
    {"question": "What are Shiftry's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Dark"},
    {"question": "What are Taillow's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Swellow's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Wingull's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Pelipper's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Ralts's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Kirlia's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Gardevoir's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Surskit's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Water"},
    {"question": "What are Masquerain's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Shroomish's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass"},
    {"question": "What are Breloom's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Fighting"},
    {"question": "What are Slakoth's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Vigoroth's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Slaking's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Nincada's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Ground"},
    {"question": "What are Ninjask's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Shedinja's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Ghost"},
    {"question": "What are Whismur's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Loudred's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Exploud's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Makuhita's type(s)?", "answer": "Fighting"},
    {"question": "What are Hariyama's type(s)?", "answer": "Fighting"},
    {"question": "What are Azurill's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Nosepass's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock"},
    {"question": "What are Skitty's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Delcatty's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Sableye's type(s)?", "answer": "Dark and Ghost"},
    {"question": "What are Mawile's type(s)?", "answer": "Steel"},
    {"question": "What are Aron's type(s)?", "answer": "Steel and Rock"},
    {"question": "What are Lairon's type(s)?", "answer": "Steel and Rock"},
    {"question": "What are Aggron's type(s)?", "answer": "Steel and Rock"},
    {"question": "What are Meditite's type(s)?", "answer": "Fighting and Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Medicham's type(s)?", "answer": "Fighting and Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Electrike's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric"},
    {"question": "What are Manectric's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric"},
    {"question": "What are Plusle's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric"},
    {"question": "What are Minun's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric"},
    {"question": "What are Volbeat's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug"},
    {"question": "What are Illumise's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug"},
    {"question": "What are Roselia's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Poison"},
    {"question": "What are Gulpin's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison"},
    {"question": "What are Swalot's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison"},
    {"question": "What are Carvanha's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Dark"},
    {"question": "What are Sharpedo's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Dark"},
    {"question": "What are Wailmer's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Wailord's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Numel's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire and Ground"},
    {"question": "What are Camerupt's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire and Ground"},
    {"question": "What are Torkoal's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire"},
    {"question": "What are Spoink's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Grumpig's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Spinda's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Trapinch's type(s)?", "answer": "Ground"},
    {"question": "What are Vibrava's type(s)?", "answer": "Ground and Dragon"},
    {"question": "What are Flygon's type(s)?", "answer": "Ground and Dragon"},
    {"question": "What are Cacnea's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass"},
    {"question": "What are Cacturne's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Dark"},
    {"question": "What are Swablu's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Altaria's type(s)?", "answer": "Dragon and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Zangoose's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Seviper's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison"},
    {"question": "What are Lunatone's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock and Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Solrock's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock and Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Barboach's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Ground"},
    {"question": "What are Whiscash's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Ground"},
    {"question": "What are Corphish's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Crawdaunt's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Dark"},
    {"question": "What are Baltoy's type(s)?", "answer": "Ground and Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Claydol's type(s)?", "answer": "Ground and Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Lileep's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock and Grass"},
    {"question": "What are Cradily's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock and Grass"},
    {"question": "What are Anorith's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock and Bug"},
    {"question": "What are Armaldo's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock and Bug"},
    {"question": "What are Feebas's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Milotic's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Castform's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Kecleon's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Shuppet's type(s)?", "answer": "Ghost"},
    {"question": "What are Banette's type(s)?", "answer": "Ghost"},
    {"question": "What are Duskull's type(s)?", "answer": "Ghost"},
    {"question": "What are Dusclops's type(s)?", "answer": "Ghost"},
    {"question": "What are Tropius's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Chimecho's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Absol's type(s)?", "answer": "Dark"},
    {"question": "What are Wynaut's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Snorunt's type(s)?", "answer": "Ice"},
    {"question": "What are Glalie's type(s)?", "answer": "Ice"},
    {"question": "What are Spheal's type(s)?", "answer": "Ice and Water"},
    {"question": "What are Sealeo's type(s)?", "answer": "Ice and Water"},
    {"question": "What are Walrein's type(s)?", "answer": "Ice and Water"},
    {"question": "What are Clamperl's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Huntail's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Gorebyss's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Relicanth's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Rock"},
    {"question": "What are Luvdisc's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Bagon's type(s)?", "answer": "Dragon"},
    {"question": "What are Shelgon's type(s)?", "answer": "Dragon"},
    {"question": "What are Salamence's type(s)?", "answer": "Dragon and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Beldum's type(s)?", "answer": "Steel and Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Metang's type(s)?", "answer": "Steel and Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Metagross's type(s)?", "answer": "Steel and Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Regirock's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock"},
    {"question": "What are Regice's type(s)?", "answer": "Ice"},
    {"question": "What are Registeel's type(s)?", "answer": "Steel"},
    {"question": "What are Latias's type(s)?", "answer": "Dragon and Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Latios's type(s)?", "answer": "Dragon and Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Kyogre's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Groudon's type(s)?", "answer": "Ground"},
    {"question": "What are Rayquaza's type(s)?", "answer": "Dragon and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Jirachi's type(s)?", "answer": "Steel and Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Deoxys [Normal Form]'s type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Deoxys [Attack Form]'s type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Deoxys [Defense Form]'s type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Deoxys [Speed Form]'s type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Turtwig's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass"},
    {"question": "What are Grotle's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass"},
    {"question": "What are Torterra's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Ground"},
    {"question": "What are Chimchar's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire"},
    {"question": "What are Monferno's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire and Fighting"},
    {"question": "What are Infernape's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire and Fighting"},
    {"question": "What are Piplup's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Prinplup's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Empoleon's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Steel"},
    {"question": "What are Starly's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Staravia's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Staraptor's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Bidoof's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Bibarel's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal and Water"},
    {"question": "What are Kricketot's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug"},
    {"question": "What are Kricketune's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug"},
    {"question": "What are Shinx's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric"},
    {"question": "What are Luxio's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric"},
    {"question": "What are Luxray's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric"},
    {"question": "What are Budew's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and "},
    {"question": "What are Roserade's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Poison"},
    {"question": "What are Cranidos's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock"},
    {"question": "What are Rampardos's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock"},
    {"question": "What are Shieldon's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock and Steel"},
    {"question": "What are Bastiodon's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock and Steel"},
    {"question": "What are Burmy's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug"},
    {"question": "What two types are Plant Cloak Wormadam?", "answer": "Bug and Grass"},
    {"question": "What two types are Sandy Cloak Wormadam?", "answer": "Bug and Ground"},
    {"question": "What two types are Trash Cloak Wormadam?", "answer": "Bug and Steel"},
    {"question": "What are Mothim's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Combee's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Vespiquen's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Pachirisu's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric"},
    {"question": "What are Buizel's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Floatzel's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Cherubi's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass"},
    {"question": "What are Cherrim's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass"},
    {"question": "What are Shellos's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Gastrodon's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Ground"},
    {"question": "What are Ambipom's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Drifloon's type(s)?", "answer": "Ghost and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Drifblim's type(s)?", "answer": "Ghost and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Buneary's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Lopunny's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Mismagius's type(s)?", "answer": "Ghost"},
    {"question": "What are Honchkrow's type(s)?", "answer": "Dark and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Glameow's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Purugly's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Chingling's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Stunky's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison and Dark"},
    {"question": "What are Skuntank's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison and Dark"},
    {"question": "What are Bronzor's type(s)?", "answer": "Steel and Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Bronzong's type(s)?", "answer": "Steel and Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Bonsly's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock"},
    {"question": "What are Mime Jr.'s type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Happiny's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Chatot's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Spiritomb's type(s)?", "answer": "Ghost and Dark"},
    {"question": "What are Gible's type(s)?", "answer": "Dragon and Ground"},
    {"question": "What are Gabite's type(s)?", "answer": "Dragon and Ground"},
    {"question": "What are Garchomp's type(s)?", "answer": "Dragon and Ground"},
    {"question": "What are Munchlax's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Riolu's type(s)?", "answer": "Fighting"},
    {"question": "What are Lucario's type(s)?", "answer": "Fighting and Steel"},
    {"question": "What are Hippopotas's type(s)?", "answer": "Ground"},
    {"question": "What are Hippowdon's type(s)?", "answer": "Ground"},
    {"question": "What are Skorupi's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison and Bug"},
    {"question": "What are Drapion's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison and Dark"},
    {"question": "What are Croagunk's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison and Fighting"},
    {"question": "What are Toxicroak's type(s)?", "answer": "Poison and Fighting"},
    {"question": "What are Carnivine's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass"},
    {"question": "What are Finneon's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Lumineon's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Mantyke's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Snover's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Ice"},
    {"question": "What are Abomasnow's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Ice"},
    {"question": "What are Weavile's type(s)?", "answer": "Dark and Ice"},
    {"question": "What are Magnezone's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric and Steel"},
    {"question": "What are Lickilicky's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Rhyperior's type(s)?", "answer": "Ground and Rock"},
    {"question": "What are Tangrowth's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass"},
    {"question": "What are Electivire's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric"},
    {"question": "What are Magmortar's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire"},
    {"question": "What are Togekiss's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Yanmega's type(s)?", "answer": "Bug and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Leafeon's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass"},
    {"question": "What are Glaceon's type(s)?", "answer": "Ice"},
    {"question": "What are Gliscor's type(s)?", "answer": "Ground and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Mamoswine's type(s)?", "answer": "Ice and Ground"},
    {"question": "What are Porygon-Z's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Gallade's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic and Fighting"},
    {"question": "What are Probopass's type(s)?", "answer": "Rock and Steel"},
    {"question": "What are Dusknoir's type(s)?", "answer": "Ghost"},
    {"question": "What are Froslass's type(s)?", "answer": "Ice and Ghost"},
    {"question": "What are Heat Rotom's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric and Ghost"},
    {"question": "What are Wash Rotom's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric and Ghost"},
    {"question": "What are Frost Rotom's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric and Ghost"},
    {"question": "What are Fan Rotom's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric and Ghost"},
    {"question": "What are Mow Rotom's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric and Ghost"},
    {"question": "What are Rotom's type(s)?", "answer": "Electric and Ghost"},
    {"question": "What are Uxie's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Mesprit's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Azelf's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Dialga's type(s)?", "answer": "Steel and Dragon"},
    {"question": "What are Palkia's type(s)?", "answer": "Water and Dragon"},
    {"question": "What are Heatran's type(s)?", "answer": "Fire and Steel"},
    {"question": "What are Regigigas's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What are Giratina's type(s)?", "answer": "Ghost and Dragon"},
    {"question": "What are Giratina's type(s)?", "answer": "Ghost and Dragon"},
    {"question": "What are Cresselia's type(s)?", "answer": "Psychic"},
    {"question": "What are Phione's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Manaphy's type(s)?", "answer": "Water"},
    {"question": "What are Darkrai's type(s)?", "answer": "Dark"},
    {"question": "What are Shaymin's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass"},
    {"question": "What are Shaymin's type(s)?", "answer": "Grass and Flying"},
    {"question": "What are Arceus's type(s)?", "answer": "Normal"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Ivysaur evolve from?", "answer": "Bulbasaur"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Charmeleon evolve from?", "answer": "Charmander"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Wartortle evolve from?", "answer": "Squirtle"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Metapod evolve from?", "answer": "Caterpie"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Kakuna evolve from?", "answer": "Weedle"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Pidgeotto evolve from?", "answer": "Pidgey"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Raticate evolve from?", "answer": "Rattata"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Fearow evolve from?", "answer": "Spearow"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Arbok evolve from?", "answer": "Ekans"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Pikachu evolve from?", "answer": "Pichu"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Sandslash evolve from?", "answer": "Sandshrew"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Nidorina evolve from?", "answer": "Nidoran(male)"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Nidorino evolve from?", "answer": "Nidoran(female)"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Clefairy evolve from?", "answer": "Cleffa"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Ninetales evolve from?", "answer": "Vulpix"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Jigglypuff evolve from?", "answer": "Igglybuff"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Golbat evolve from?", "answer": "Zubat"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Gloom evolve from?", "answer": "Oddish"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Parasect evolve from?", "answer": "Paras"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Venomoth evolve from?", "answer": "Venonat"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Dugtrio evolve from?", "answer": "Diglett"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Persian evolve from?", "answer": "Meowth"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Golduck evolve from?", "answer": "Psyduck"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Primeape evolve from?", "answer": "Mankey"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Arcanine evolve from?", "answer": "Growlithe"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Poliwhirl evolve from?", "answer": "Poliwag"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Kadabra evolve from?", "answer": "Abra"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Machoke evolve from?", "answer": "Machop"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Weepinbell evolve from?", "answer": "Bellsprout"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Tentacruel evolve from?", "answer": "Tentacool"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Graveler evolve from?", "answer": "Geodude"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Rapidash evolve from?", "answer": "Ponyta"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Slowbro evolve from?", "answer": "Slowpoke"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Slowking evolve from?", "answer": "Slowpoke"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Magneton evolve from?", "answer": "Magnemite"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Dodrio evolve from?", "answer": "Doduo"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Dewgong evolve from?", "answer": "Seel"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Muk evolve from?", "answer": "Grimer"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Cloyster evolve from?", "answer": "Shellder"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Haunter evolve from?", "answer": "Gastly"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Steelix evolve from?", "answer": "Onix"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Hypno evolve from?", "answer": "Drowzee"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Kingler evolve from?", "answer": "Krabby"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Electrode evolve from?", "answer": "Voltorb"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Exeggutor evolve from?", "answer": "Exeggcute"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Marowak evolve from?", "answer": "Cubone"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Hitmonlee evolve from?", "answer": "Tyrogue"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Hitmonchan evolve from?", "answer": "Tyrogue"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Hitmontop evolve from?", "answer": "Tyrogue"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Lickilicky evolve from?", "answer": "Lickitung"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Weezing evolve from?", "answer": "Koffing"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Rhydon evolve from?", "answer": "Rhyhorn"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Chansey evolve from?", "answer": "Happiny"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Tangrowth evolve from?", "answer": "Tangela"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Seadra evolve from?", "answer": "Horsea"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Seaking evolve from?", "answer": "Goldeen"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Starmie evolve from?", "answer": "Staryu"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Mr. Mime evolve from?", "answer": "Mime Jr."},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Scizor evolve from?", "answer": "Scyther"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Jynx evolve from?", "answer": "Smoochum"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Electabuzz evolve from?", "answer": "Elekid"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Magmar evolve from?", "answer": "Magby"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Gyarados evolve from?", "answer": "Magikarp"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Vaporeon evolve from?", "answer": "Eevee"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Jolteon evolve from?", "answer": "Eevee"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Flareon evolve from?", "answer": "Eevee"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Espeon evolve from?", "answer": "Eevee"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Umbreon evolve from?", "answer": "Eevee"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Leafeon evolve from?", "answer": "Eevee"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Glaceon evolve from?", "answer": "Eevee"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Porygon2 evolve from?", "answer": "Porygon"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Omastar evolve from?", "answer": "Omanyte"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Kabutops evolve from?", "answer": "Kabuto"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Snorlax evolve from?", "answer": "Munchlax"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Dragonair evolve from?", "answer": "Dratini"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Bayleef evolve from?", "answer": "Chikorita"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Quilava evolve from?", "answer": "Cyndaquil"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Croconaw evolve from?", "answer": "Totodile"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Furret evolve from?", "answer": "Sentret"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Noctowl evolve from?", "answer": "Hoothoot"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Ledian evolve from?", "answer": "Ledyba"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Ariados evolve from?", "answer": "Spinarak"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Lanturn evolve from?", "answer": "Chinchou"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Togetic evolve from?", "answer": "Togepi"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Xatu evolve from?", "answer": "Natu"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Flaaffy evolve from?", "answer": "Mareep"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Marill evolve from?", "answer": "Azurill"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Sudowoodo evolve from?", "answer": "Bonsly"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Skiploom evolve from?", "answer": "Hoppip"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Ambipom evolve from?", "answer": "Aipom"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Sunflora evolve from?", "answer": "Sunkern"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Yanmega evolve from?", "answer": "Yanma"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Quagsire evolve from?", "answer": "Wooper"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Honchkrow evolve from?", "answer": "Murkrow"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Mismagius evolve from?", "answer": "Misdreavus"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Wobbuffet evolve from?", "answer": "Wynaut"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Forretress evolve from?", "answer": "Pineco"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Gliscor evolve from?", "answer": "Gligar"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Granbull evolve from?", "answer": "Snubbull"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Weavile evolve from?", "answer": "Sneasel"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Ursaring evolve from?", "answer": "Teddiursa"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Magcargo evolve from?", "answer": "Slugma"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Piloswine evolve from?", "answer": "Swinub"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Octillery evolve from?", "answer": "Remoraid"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Mantine evolve from?", "answer": "Mantyke"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Houndoom evolve from?", "answer": "Houndour"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Donphan evolve from?", "answer": "Phanpy"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Pupitar evolve from?", "answer": "Larvitar"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Grovyle evolve from?", "answer": "Treecko"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Combusken evolve from?", "answer": "Torchic"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Marshtomp evolve from?", "answer": "Mudkip"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Mightyena evolve from?", "answer": "Poochyena"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Linoone evolve from?", "answer": "Zigzagoon"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Silcoon evolve from?", "answer": "Wurmple"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Cascoon evolve from?", "answer": "Wurmple"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Lombre evolve from?", "answer": "Lotad"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Nuzleaf evolve from?", "answer": "Seedot"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Swellow evolve from?", "answer": "Taillow"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Pelipper evolve from?", "answer": "Wingull"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Kirlia evolve from?", "answer": "Ralts"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Masquerain evolve from?", "answer": "Surskit"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Breloom evolve from?", "answer": "Shroomish"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Vigoroth evolve from?", "answer": "Slakoth"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Ninjask evolve from?", "answer": "Nincada"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Shedinja evolve from?", "answer": "Nincada"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Loudred evolve from?", "answer": "Whismur"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Hariyama evolve from?", "answer": "Makuhita"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Probopass evolve from?", "answer": "Nosepass"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Delcatty evolve from?", "answer": "Skitty"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Lairon evolve from?", "answer": "Aron"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Medicham evolve from?", "answer": "Meditite"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Manectric evolve from?", "answer": "Electrike"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Roselia evolve from?", "answer": "Budew"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Swalot evolve from?", "answer": "Gulpin"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Sharpedo evolve from?", "answer": "Carvanha"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Wailord evolve from?", "answer": "Wailmer"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Camerupt evolve from?", "answer": "Numel"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Grumpig evolve from?", "answer": "Spoink"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Vibrava evolve from?", "answer": "Trapinch"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Cacturne evolve from?", "answer": "Cacnea"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Altaria evolve from?", "answer": "Swablu"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Whiscash evolve from?", "answer": "Barboach"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Crawdaunt evolve from?", "answer": "Corphish"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Claydol evolve from?", "answer": "Baltoy"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Cradily evolve from?", "answer": "Lileep"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Armaldo evolve from?", "answer": "Anorith"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Milotic evolve from?", "answer": "Feebas"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Banette evolve from?", "answer": "Shuppet"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Dusclops evolve from?", "answer": "Duskull"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Chimecho evolve from?", "answer": "Chingling"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Glalie evolve from?", "answer": "Snorunt"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Froslass evolve from?", "answer": "Snorunt"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Sealeo evolve from?", "answer": "Spheal"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Huntail evolve from?", "answer": "Clamperl"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Gorebyss evolve from?", "answer": "Clamperl"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Shelgon evolve from?", "answer": "Bagon"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Metang evolve from?", "answer": "Beldum"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Grotle evolve from?", "answer": "Turtwig"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Monferno evolve from?", "answer": "Chimchar"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Prinplup evolve from?", "answer": "Piplup"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Staravia evolve from?", "answer": "Starly"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Bibarel evolve from?", "answer": "Bidoof"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Kricketune evolve from?", "answer": "Kricketot"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Luxio evolve from?", "answer": "Shinx"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Rampardos evolve from?", "answer": "Cranidos"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Bastiodon evolve from?", "answer": "Shieldon"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Wormadam evolve from?", "answer": "Burmy"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Mothim evolve from?", "answer": "Burmy"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Vespiquen evolve from?", "answer": "Combee"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Floatzel evolve from?", "answer": "Buizel"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Cherrim evolve from?", "answer": "Cherubi"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Gastrodon evolve from?", "answer": "Shellos"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Drifblim evolve from?", "answer": "Drifloon"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Lopunny evolve from?", "answer": "Buneary"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Purugly evolve from?", "answer": "Glameow"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Skuntank evolve from?", "answer": "Stunky"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Bronzong evolve from?", "answer": "Bronzor"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Gabite evolve from?", "answer": "Gible"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Lucario evolve from?", "answer": "Riolu"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Hippowdon evolve from?", "answer": "Hippopotas"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Drapion evolve from?", "answer": "Skorupi"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Toxicroak evolve from?", "answer": "Croagunk"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Lumineon evolve from?", "answer": "Finneon"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Abomasnow evolve from?", "answer": "Snover"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Venusaur evolve from?", "answer": "Ivysaur"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Charizard evolve from?", "answer": "Charmeleon"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Blastoise evolve from?", "answer": "Wartortle"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Butterfree evolve from?", "answer": "Metapod"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Beedrill evolve from?", "answer": "Kakuna"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Pidgeot evolve from?", "answer": "Pidgeotto"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Raichu evolve from?", "answer": "Pikachu"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Nidoqueen evolve from?", "answer": "Nidorina"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Nidoking evolve from?", "answer": "Nidorino"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Clefable evolve from?", "answer": "Clefairy"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Wigglytuff evolve from?", "answer": "Jigglypuff"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Crobat evolve from?", "answer": "Golbat"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Vileplume evolve from?", "answer": "Gloom"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Bellossom evolve from?", "answer": "Gloom"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Poliwrath evolve from?", "answer": "Poliwhirl"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Politoed evolve from?", "answer": "Poliwhirl"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Alakazam evolve from?", "answer": "Kadabra"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Machamp evolve from?", "answer": "Machoke"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Victreebel evolve from?", "answer": "Weepinbell"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Golem evolve from?", "answer": "Graveler"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Magnezone evolve from?", "answer": "Magneton"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Gengar evolve from?", "answer": "Haunter"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Rhyperior evolve from?", "answer": "Rhydon"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Blissey evolve from?", "answer": "Chansey"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Kingdra evolve from?", "answer": "Seadra"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Electivire evolve from?", "answer": "Electabuzz"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Magmortar evolve from?", "answer": "Magmar"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Porygon-Z evolve from?", "answer": "Porygon2"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Dragonite evolve from?", "answer": "Dragonair"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Meganium evolve from?", "answer": "Bayleef"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Typhlosion evolve from?", "answer": "Quilava"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Feraligatr evolve from?", "answer": "Croconaw"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Togekiss evolve from?", "answer": "Togetic"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Ampharos evolve from?", "answer": "Flaaffy"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Azumarill evolve from?", "answer": "Marill"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Jumpluff evolve from?", "answer": "Skiploom"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Mamoswine evolve from?", "answer": "Piloswine"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Tyranitar evolve from?", "answer": "Pupitar"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Sceptile evolve from?", "answer": "Grovyle"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Blaziken evolve from?", "answer": "Combusken"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Swampert evolve from?", "answer": "Marshtomp"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Beautifly evolve from?", "answer": "Silcoon"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Dustox evolve from?", "answer": "Cascoon"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Ludicolo evolve from?", "answer": "Lombre"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Shiftry evolve from?", "answer": "Nuzleaf"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Gardevoir evolve from?", "answer": "Kirlia"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Gallade evolve from?", "answer": "Kirlia"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Slaking evolve from?", "answer": "Vigoroth"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Exploud evolve from?", "answer": "Loudred"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Aggron evolve from?", "answer": "Lairon"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Roserade evolve from?", "answer": "Roselia"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Flygon evolve from?", "answer": "Vibrava"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Dusknoir evolve from?", "answer": "Dusclops"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Walrein evolve from?", "answer": "Sealeo"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Salamence evolve from?", "answer": "Shelgon"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Metagross evolve from?", "answer": "Metang"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Torterra evolve from?", "answer": "Grotle"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Infernape evolve from?", "answer": "Monferno"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Empoleon evolve from?", "answer": "Prinplup"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Staraptor evolve from?", "answer": "Staravia"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Luxray evolve from?", "answer": "Luxio"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon does Garchomp evolve from?", "answer": "Gabite"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon are known as The Legendary birds?", "answer": "Articuno Zapdos and Moltres"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon are known as The Mew Duo?", "answer": "Mewtwo and Mew"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon are known as The Legendary Beasts?", "answer": "Raikou Entei and Suicune"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon are known as The Tower Duo?", "answer": "Lugia and Ho-Oh"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon are known as The Legendary Golems?", "answer": "Regirock Regice and Registeel"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon are known as The Eon duo?", "answer": "Latias and Latios"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon are known as The Weather Trio?", "answer": "Kyogre Groudon and Rayquaza"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon are known as The Lake guardians?", "answer": "Uxie Mesprit and Azelf"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon are known as The Legendary dragons?", "answer": "Dialga Palkia and Giratina"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon are known as The Lunar duo?", "answer": "Cresselia and Darkrai"},
    {"question": "What Pokemon are known as The Sea guardians?", "answer": "Phione and Manaphy"},
    {"question": "Articuno, Zapdos, and Moltres are known as...?", "answer": "The Legendary birds"},
    {"question": "Mewtwo, and Mew are known as...?", "answer": "The Mew Duo"},
    {"question": "Raikou, Entei, and Suicune are known as...?", "answer": "The Legendary Beasts"},
    {"question": "Lugia, and Ho-Oh are known as...?", "answer": "The Tower Duo"},
    {"question": "Regirock, Regice, and Registeel are known as...?", "answer": "The Legendary Golems"},
    {"question": "Latias, and Latios are known as...?", "answer": "The Eon duo"},
    {"question": "Kyogre, Groudon, and Rayquaza are known as...?", "answer": "The Weather Trio"},
    {"question": "Uxie, Mesprit, and Azelf are known as...?", "answer": "The Lake guardians"},
    {"question": "Dialga, Palkia, and Giratina are known as...?", "answer": "The Legendary dragons"},
    {"question": "Cresselia, and Darkrai are known as...?", "answer": "The Lunar duo"},
    {"question": "Phione, and Manaphy are known as...?", "answer": "The Sea guardians"}
  ]
}